(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Signature choreography takeover match)
(BADA 4, INGYOO 5)
This is brutal.
I was overflowing with confidence.
This is the first time I lost my choreography...
and failed to win my rival's.
I was confused.
(Signature choreography takeover match)
(Back Koo Young 9, Kasper 0)
Something's gone wrong.
(Heavy-hearted)
I started feeling anxious...
after seeing the public's reaction.
"He's wobbling too much. Is he an earthworm?"
"That doesn't look any different from the original."
(Kasper's new "Love Shot" received harsh criticisms.)
(When announcing the result)
(He didn't receive a single vote.)
On top of that, it was a total defeat.
(Looking away)
Everyone turned their backs on me.
I wanted to hide.
(Simeez 9, Renan 0)
This is tough.
Is it okay to turn off the light?
The feeling of all that time I spent on "Armageddon..."
felt denied.
That really upset me.
(Heavy-hearted)
(Yelling)
(Glancing)
(Cheers cut through the silence.)
It's over now.
I was happy to hear...
that my name will appear as a choreographer.
I was like, "What? Maybe I did a really good job."
I'm going to win the Director's Credit next.
(INGYOO's room is filled with his humming.)
It felt amazing.
(On cloud nine)
(Laughing)
It requires my choreography in general.
The situation is...
in my favor.
I'm going to enjoy it and have more fun.
(BABYZOO 5, NaiN 4)
I won the choreographer title.
And I need to win the Director Credit too.
I began planning immediately.
(He's about to crush the mission song.)
(Planning mode)
After winning, it got me thinking,
I do have a weapon,
but Hash's good at directing.
I can never be off guard.
I think my performance...
mixed with MIN JUN's choreography...
will feel cooler and fresher.
The signature choreography is a bummer.
It's not over until it's over.
It'll be a matter...
of how creatively each person handles it.
I feel confident...
about developing it and turning the choreography I lost even cooler.
If I lose again,
it'll be like getting kicked out...
to the street naked.
I'll win by 9 to 0 this time.
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(To be continued)
All the results have been announced...
for the signature choreography takeover match.
The first choreographers to have their names...
on the credit board for choreographer are...
Simeez, BABYZOO,
JEONG MIN JUN, INGYOO,
and Back Koo Young.
Now, both signature parts...
will compose of the winner's choreography.
You'll work based on that.
It'll be obvious that I'm working on someone else's choreography.
It's not even my choreography.
My pride isn't hurt. It's rotting.
I've hit rock bottom.
Although I lost my choreography,
I'll win the director title.
I'll get the Director Credit.
In the last run to determine the final director,
the judges will evaluate you...
based on your choreography,
a number of dancers, space structure,
and the ability to direct a large group.
Judges' evaluation?
This is a directing battle.
I might not become a director?
That's not good. I can never accept that.
The cards aren't in my hands.
I'm worried about it.
I can't lose it. Losing that will be a nightmare.
Becoming a director with my choreography won't be easy.
It'll be hard. It'll be tough.
Now, you'll cast dancers...
to complete the work with you.
Oh, we get to cast them?
Because everyone wants to cast talented dancers,
a battle will break out.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
(To complete the final stage)
I will tell you how the dancer casting works.
There will be a total of 80 dancers per round.
You'll choose five from each round...
with a total of 40 dancers to form a team.
Depending on the direction of your work,
you may cast ten additional dancers.
A team can have up to 50 dancers.
You must come up...
with the best strategy to complete your work.
It's either one.
Either excel or make it even more brutal.
"Renan's the best director ever."
I will have to do my best.
Well, thanks for your choreography.
But I am the director.
(Next morning)
(Back to Directors' Lab)
Dancer casting?
That's the most important.
A director could create a masterpiece...
if they make good use of talented dancers.
Dancers over a choreography.
Dancer casting is the key.
What matters the most in dancer casting is...
a body that can absorb anything.
Spella? No way. She's mine for sure.
I'm good at making use of the dancers' strength.
Dancers with strong presence and identity.
I want someone with ambition and distinct character.
Is this the list of dancers for me and Hash?
Lip J?
(Lip J?)
I fell silent.
What is Lip J doing in there?
For real?
Lip J is good.
She's already earned the public's approval.
Lip J was number one on my list.
I have to get her for sure.
I want to work with Rian so bad.
(Rian!)
(Simeez runs to Rian as soon as she sees her name.)
- I can never lose Rian. - I choose Rian.
(Renan also sees Rian.)
I have to win this time. I couldn't give up.
For sure.
HANYA members for sure.
Since he got the signature choreography, he'll give up on this.
I can never give up.
Why would I? Never.
Who said that?
Wait. Lee Jung?
(Laughing)
Lee Jung's here.
Wait. Mood Dog?
(Passing out)
This is crazy.
(Mood Dog of YGX participated as a rookie class main dancer...)
(in "Street Man Fighter.")
(BABYZOO, Lee Jung, and Mood Dog are...)
(known for being friends.)
I can never give up on them.
I'm going for Lee Jung.
Wait a minute.
I'm not as kind as you think, you know?
First, I need Nino.
It's weird to see Nino...
in someone else's team.
So what are you going to do?
Are you going there or staying here?
(A fierce battle over Nino)
Oh, Shuri?
All directors here want him.
- Shuri's coming? - Shuri?
I want Shuri.
- I want him too. - Oh, Shuri.
- No. - No way.
You can't take him.
I've worked with him before.
Shuri, I live in Japan.
What are you saying? Shuri's mine.
- Hey. - What are you doing?
- He's mine. - I know.
I brought him from Japan.
He's like my son.
(The Japanese dancer who captivated Korea's dance scene)
(Shuri's known for his big physique and strong expression.)
I call him a weapon. My weapon.
Vata's my highest priority.
Vata's here too.
Oh, Tatter!
She's the anchor of my team.
She'll be my highest priority.
I can cast Tatter?
Tatter is my highest priority.
If he takes Tatter?
Then she'll be my spy.
I'll tell her to report...
every detail of INGYOO's plan.
(Ten chairs for directors are...)
(placed in Directors' Lab.)
Oh, there are chairs.
(And the dummies...)
(come alive.)
(An endless rows of dancers)
(Global dancers gathered for Street World Fighter: Directors' War.)
(1-on-1 Signature Mission with 400 Dancers)
- I'm scared. - This is so much pressure.
(Gasping)
This is crazy.
Gosh.
(The first 80 dancers have entered.)
So they're the first round of dancers.
(Exclaiming)
This is awesome.
The first match is...
Simeez versus Renan.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission Dancer Casting)
This is going to be fun.
- Isn't that Rian? - That's Rian.
She's a very famous dancer...
and a dazzling player.
She's a very strong performer.
(Rian is strong at choreography performance.)
There's Spella.
I know. Spella's here too.
Spella's good at soft moves...
as well as strong moves.
I think she's good at performing.
I see JAYME.
Don't you think you're eyeing someone who's too good?
JAYME has a very wide range.
He nails it just by standing there.
He's one and only.
We might end up fighting, pulling each other's hair to get him.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'm Simeez. - I'm Renan.
My signature song is IVE's "BANG BANG."
And Renan's signature song is...
aespa's "Armageddon."
The song's been rearranged.
The song is very intense in general.
The final theme is destruction and awakening.
The final battle.
I really liked Varang...
from "Avatar: Fire and Ash."
That's what I'm thinking about in terms of visualization.
When I heard her theme, I was kind of worried.
I'll tell you about my concept.
I wanted to express...
someone who lives the way he wants...
regardless of what others say.
The biggest difference is...
that I have a clear concept.
Her direction is a shame.
Simeez's concept was clear.
I was like, "That sounds cool."
I could picture it in my head.
I can't tell what Renan wants to do.
Because I must win,
I need dancers with definite style...
and abilities to pull off the dance.
Although I lost the signature choreography,
to turn it around,
I need good dancers.
First.
(Who will get to cast first?)
(1 hour ago)
What do you want to do?
Is there any dancer you must have?
Unless we had the same dancer candidates,
it didn't matter who went first.
I'm thinking BIGGY and JAYME.
I need Rian for sure.
And I need Spella.
I want BIGGY and JAYME.
How can she do that?
That's everyone.
How can she be so selfish?
How can she be so inconsiderate?
They're here for me.
I don't want to lose them.
I'm planning on many unique angles.
I had no intention of giving in.
JAYME has his own style.
I need someone more than just being a good dancer.
I needed someone with star quality and personality.
I just couldn't give up on JAYME.
Dancer casting is important...
because I like creating main characters.
So for Rian, JAYME, and Spella,
I plan to give them characters.
I was planning to...
give them a different style among the other dancers.
But...
when I do something hip during the song,
I need BIGGY.
I can never give in.
I need BIGGY too.
This is so stressful.
- BIGGY and JAYME? - Yes.
JAYME looks cool even when he just stretches his arm.
He could be my strong weapon.
So I didn't want to lose him.
(Groaning)
This is crazy.
I knew going first was more advantageous.
Because I couldn't lose them.
I knew I had to get them first.
First. Choreographer Renan...
will begin casting the dancers.
(Renan casts the dancers first.)
Simeez! You lost it.
I got the signature choreography,
and I can always come up with new characters. So I gave in.
The first person to cast is...
JAYME.
(Grunting)
I really want to work with you.
I'd like to cast you.
No.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Seeing her taking JAYME in front of me,
it got me thinking, "Why did I give up JAYME?"
(Scanning)
It still upsets me.
I still regret...
not taking JAYME the most.
Why did I do that? I must've lost it at the time.
And BIGGY.
I'll cast her.
- Are you casting me? - Yes.
(The second dancer she casts is BIGGY.)
No. She's taking everyone.
Why did I let her go first?
If I could go back in time,
I would go first.
I was so happy...
to cast good dancers first.
JEONG MIN JUN versus Hash.
We'll now begin the dancer casting.
(The dancers are warming up.)
(Welcoming)
(Good luck.)
(Greeting)
Who's that?
(A dancer with 19 years of experience?)
I said hi to Lip J.
- Is that Lip J? - Yes.
Lip J's here?
(Lip J of PROWDMON)
She's the top waacker in Korea.
Every gesture she makes is charismatic.
The first dancer to choose was Lip J.
Lip J was my highest priority.
(1 hour ago)
What do we do? Who are you going to pick?
First, Lip J.
Really?
But I should have her.
(Laughing)
Then whoever picks Lip J gives up on five people.
(Give up on five dancers.)
Let's spin the roulette.
(They suddenly spin the roulette.)
Gosh.
(Nervous)
Please.
(JEONG MIN JUN wins.)
(Groaning)
(Joy)
But why?
I'd like to work...
with Korea's top waacker, Lip J.
I'd really appreciate it...
- if you could join me. - Are you casting me?
Yes. I'd really appreciate it.
Can I dance?
Let's go.
(Lip J's ceremony)
So cool!
(Featured by Street World Fighter: Directors' War waacker, BABYZOO)
(Who can refuse this combination?)
Oh, my gosh.
(Immersed)
(I'll show you what waacking is.)
Yes.
What? They're like twins.
(In sync)
Yes!
(A fantastic collaboration of Lip J and BABYZOO)
(Amazed)
That's unbelievable.
I kind of sighed because I was jealous.
I've gained a powerful ally.
(JEONG MIN JUN's first dancer to cast is Lip J.)
I have someone on my mind.
(While going over the dancer profiles)
Jung Min?
He was a member of MIN JUN's team.
I knew I had to get Jung Min...
since he was close to MIN JUN.
I have to do MIN JUN's choreography in the end.
From what I heard, he pulls off MIN JUN's choreography...
better than MIN JUN does.
So I'm going to make him stand out...
when he does MIN JUN's choreography.
Please.
(Laughing)
- Please. No! - MIN JUN's...
I choose MIN JUN's best friend.
- Yes. - No.
- Who is he? - He was a member...
- Really? - of MIN JUN's team.
- No. - Sorry.
(Hash's first dancer to cast is Jung Min.)
I'll treat you nicely.
I was worried about Jung Min the most.
I knew I had to cast him.
She strategically took my card.
Because Hash cast Jung Min...
(Anxious)
I selected a few.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
No.
Who is he?
I found a dancer from COME HERE.
I'm taking this card.
(I won't be beaten.)
I'm looking forward to working with you.
(JEONG MIN JUN's second dancer to cast is TAEM.)
(In despair)
MIN JUN just cast a member of COME HERE.
You're right. What are they doing?
They should cast their own team first.
- That's what I mean. - If they're in different teams,
it's a disaster.
Gosh. What am I going to do?
It felt like the end of the world.
We ended up competing...
with each other's most precious team members.
What am I going to do?
I'm different from others.
I'm going to keep adding my styles...
and come up with a performance that only I can do.
I can hold my own...
because I have Lip J with me.
(Max confidence)
I totally stole Renan's signature choreography.
It's driving me crazy.
My anger was up here.
I had to win this time.
I'm confident about a large group performance.
I want to show the difference...
in the signature choreography structure.
Although she took my signature choreography,
I'll put my name...
in the Director Credit.
I really want this of all time.
I'm going to pour in...
everything I have and everything I'm good at.
Because I'm here to fight as a director.
I'll make it a clean sweep.
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
Now, we'll have time to teach the new choreography...
of "Armageddon..."
that won the signature choreography takeover match.
(Simeez begins teaching the new "Armageddon" choreography.)
I have sad news.
Simeez and I had a mission.
We were supposed to steal...
each other's signature choreography.
I had a clean sweep.
Awesome.
My choreography won't be used.
It hurt my pride...
to say that I lost it...
to someone else.
It made me really dogged.
I'd better nail it,
so everyone would want to join my team.
- I want to prove it. - You want to prove it?
That my choreography is better.
A director's job starts with teaching.
I need to teach my choreography in a fun, flavorful way.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(Clapping without looking)
I'll teach it to you super fast and head out.
Play the music, please. I'll show you.
(Renan also has to learn the choreography from Simeez.)
Music.
It felt a bit awkward. I was intimidated without realizing it.
Let me play the track for you once.
When teaching, giving a shocking demonstration has a real impact.
Learning the choreography of "Armageddon..."
from another choreographer...
was really stressful.
"This is the fun choreography you are going to dance."
I need to show it to them in an impressive way.
(Amazed)
(The new "Armageddon," reborn in Simeez's style)
Honestly, she's good.
- Right. - She's so talented.
She's really cool. She's incredible.
All the dancers loved it,
so I felt a bit down.
I want to build a different formation...
to prove that Renan is the better director...
after all.
My goal during the lesson...
was to assess the dancers.
They followed along better than I expected.
But while they execute it well,
they didn't seem to have any distinct features.
Their individuality and charm fall flat.
My dancers have strong, distinct characters.
I need those with solid technique.
Scorpion.
This is like "Star King."
Where have you been all this time?
I thought I should show how people across various genres...
with great and strong individuality can unite into one.
It looks like she's trying to blend multiple genres together.
If you mix too many colors in,
it just turns into a weird, muddy color.
The most crucial thing in a mega crew performance is...
the synchronization among the dancers.
Working on all those details in a short period of time?
That's impossible.
She's going to regret it.
Since it's an all-genre mega crew performance,
I need to make versatile use of technical formations.
(Team Simeez's practice room)
(Floor technique)
Yes!
(Acrobatics)
Technical styles like tutting, locking, waacking.
I want to use everyone's personal weapons as our specialties.
We're going to look so cool.
The choreography is amazing.
Please express yourselves.
(How will Team Simeez, blending various genres, turn out?)
(Out of sync)
Maybe it's because we focused heavily on individuality.
We do need to sync up our timing a bit.
Since it's a mega crew mission,
we'll need time to get in sync.
Since my team had distinct characters...
and many different genres,
the movements didn't seem to sync well.
(And so, Team Simeez started working on the details.)
I think we should practice here more.
(Stepping back)
(Spotted)
This way, Rina.
You need to move in further here, Rina.
Rina!
(Rina is called out repeatedly for consecutive mistakes.)
I cast Rina because of her technique.
(Where have you been all this time?)
Her technical skills were great,
but she ended up in the front row for the most crucial part.
Rina, you have to practice more. Please.
Practice. Okay?
No more mistakes from here on out.
- Okay. - Okay.
She'd been locked into one specific style for so long.
She'd worn the same clothes for decades,
so trying on a different style was tough for her, of course.
I'm in trouble. This is our biggest hurdle.
(The mistakes keep happening even after time passes.)
It's this way, not that way.
Your foot.
This is crazy. Is it even going to work?
It was pure despair.
Everything had to be perfectly in sync,
but the moves weren't coming together.
Rina!
I really didn't want to get on Rina's case.
Can I have a moment with you, Rina?
I think your timing is...
a little bit different.
I think we have to change your position...
- with another person. - Okay.
Messing up in the front row...
throws off the entire choreography.
I was having a total mental breakdown.
(Groaning)
We can do this!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Hang in there, Simeez!)
I really want us to pull this off.
Maybe I shouldn't have gone with all-genre dancers.
Casting dancers is also part of a director's capability.
Let's work on the intro choreography first.
I think it would be great if we did it like crazy people.
I want to bring out the crazy vibe.
The intro. To me, that's my second highlight.
I consider it a second chorus.
We will start like this.
(Dropping to our knees right from the start?)
Yes.
What?
What's going on?
We'll dance while moving like this.
- Oh, my goodness. - A bit like a crazy person.
That's crazy.
I got absolute chills.
That psycho-like madness is the point of my choreography.
I thought about how to make it look unhinged.
I was resting in my hotel room all drowsy.
And I suddenly tried moving like this.
As soon as I saw it, I went, "This is it."
We're going to win for sure.
This is nice. We look crazy.
What if we try lying all the way down?
The 1st 5 seconds must be enchanting for people to keep watching.
This is pretty.
The intro decides everything.
(Chills)
(That's how Renan's signature crazy intro was born.)
Are you a genius?
This is so cool.
The dancers seem so well in sync.
I think we can win this.
(I think we can win this.)
(Directors' Room for Simeez)
The formation is way too off. What do I do?
No matter how many times we adjusted it, it was off.
It kept going right back to square one.
I think it's my mistake that I went all-genre.
What a headache.
I want to create a truly legendary video.
I just really want to do well.
- You're good. - I will be good.
Don't worry. It'll turn out great.
I took a sneak peek at the practice video.
- Varang. - Varang.
Like this.
It fits your face well, which I really like.
It could come off as a bit childish.
That's why I tried not to overemphasize the concept.
I just want to show that I was inspired by it.
You can emphasize it. It suits you well.
There's an area of directing I excel at,
which is concept utilization.
Using props is my strong suit.
I reworked the formation to match...
the concept properly.
(Perfect synchronization)
When you have something in your hands,
even simple movements look...
visually full and satisfying.
- There's something I'd like to get. - Yes.
I need something like flat boards.
I think it will look great.
(Amazed)
It felt like the grandeur was multiplied.
When utilizing props, I figured...
I should compete through visuals and formation...
rather than dancing.
Something's popping up on screen. There's going to be something.
The 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission Practice Video.
Oh, my goodness!
Are they shaking our minds like this?
Honestly, that's what I wanted to see the most.
This is going to be fun.
Oh, gosh.
"Predict the win or loss and directors for each matchup."
I have to win. I put everything into making this.
The one I'm most curious about is Simeez and Renan.
It looked like they were doing something grand.
It must be super flashy, true to Simeez's style.
They're watching mine now.
(Simeez's choreography practice)
Gosh, hang on.
Right from the very start.
This is insane.
She managed to get something incredible.
She seems skilled at using props.
The solar panels look great.
Is that Waackxxxy?
Locking!
In the newly arranged section,
the dance genres were utilized so appropriately.
Watching the beginning, I was a little worried.
I was thinking, "Oh no, what do we do?"
But as it progressed toward the end, I felt like...
we actually had a shot.
But the synchronization is the issue.
As it went on, I noticed that they were out of sync.
Anyway, our team is well in sync.
Let's go, Renan.
Starting with the hand movements?
(Renan's choreography practice)
My goodness. That's so terrifying.
Look at this. They look like ghosts.
(100 percent satisfied)
The intro is so overwhelming.
The intro has an incredible impact.
I don't really feel much of a clear concept.
It feels like the tension drops during the "Bang Bang" part.
They show the entire "Bang Bang" part from the front.
It's like a dragging point.
It seems she placed a lot of weight on utilizing JAYME.
I don't think she fully understands JAYME's strengths.
JAYME isn't the type who shines when doing the same choreography.
The predicted credits?
I think our team's greatest strength is our synchronization.
I came up with such an impactful intro.
I'm going to win this no matter what.
I cannot lose.
I have to take the Director Credit.
Those who love crazy...
and high-impact vibes...
will probably love mine.
I think it comes down to a matter of personal taste.
It's not about personal taste. I want to be...
overwhelmingly better.
(Shocked)
(Sighing)
I assumed I would win.
I was sure it would be me.
Choreographer, Simeez. Director, Simeez.
I'm sad because the opponent is so strong.
Gosh, that was too loud.
Having my name listed on both the Director...
and Choreographer Credits...
felt amazing.
Was I being too excited?
(Shouting)
(Simeez's shout echoes all the way into Renan's room.)
(Feeling bitter)
I kept wondering why things weren't working out,
and my confidence hit rock bottom.
I came here to be ambitious, after all.
I got the Choreographer Credit to claim this.
"The momentum in the later part leaves much to be desired."
"The flow drags during the 'Bang Bang' part."
"It's disappointing that the tension drops toward the end,"
"causing the focus to fade." I see.
(Troubled)
There are standout dancers on the team,
but the way they were utilized didn't seem good enough.
There's a specific dance I could've showcased in the front,
so performing the full choreography felt like a waste.
It's a dance break,
but I don't think it feels distinct from what came before.
If I get just ten seconds, I can tear up the entire stage.
It's disappointing that I appear for only about 0.5 seconds.
I wonder if that was a good card to play.
Could you please turn off the lights?
(The lights are out in Renan's Directors' Room.)
Even if she hears it the day before...
I mean, your mindset can awaken,
but it's hard to turn the tables with the piece itself in a day.
(Renan is lost in deep thought.)
(The night of the mid-point review)
It's not easy.
(Sighing)
I was really confident,
but why isn't this working out?
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
(Who will claim the Director Credit?)
(The 10 choreographers are entering the stage.)
Once I stepped up there, the nerves really hit me.
I don't think I've felt this nervous anytime recently.
Simeez is here.
Why does she have to be right next to me?
It did get on my nerves.
She's so scary.
She's terrifying.
Simeez, it looks like you're going to eat Renan alive.
Seeing Simeez's outfit,
the quality was so high...
that I felt quite intimidated.
I have to win.
There's this particular feeling, you know.
The burning rage of being wronged.
There is a distinct fury known only to those who have lost.
I am going to win this, no matter what.
Hash is here.
MIN JUN had a gentler look in his eyes at first.
But the look in his eyes changed. He looks so determined...
to beat me down.
If I said I was confident, it would be a lie.
You can never underestimate someone with an extensive career.
I'm keeping a close eye on her.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hello.
(Looking away)
I saw an uncomfortable energy, so I tried to stay relaxed.
(Exclaiming)
Deep down, I felt an intense sense of crisis...
and competitiveness,
but I hid it and kept practicing mental control.
(Surprised)
The judges are here.
Who are they?
(Surprised)
(The first judge for the Last Run enters.)
(Passionate welcome)
(Monika left a powerful impression through "Street Woman Fighter.")
A director with distinct visual pictures, clear themes,
and storytelling.
A director who is active across various fields...
and respected by everyone.
Monika!
(Heart)
When Monika came out, I felt a slight twinge.
Because Lip J was on MIN JUN's team.
We haven't been in touch for five days.
Please make sure to spread the word that I'll be fair.
She is sharp, detail-oriented, and decisive.
I thought she would deliver a decisive opinion for one side.
(Next, the second judge for the Last Run enters.)
(Jae Won?)
Jae Won!
It's Jae Won. This is crazy.
He is someone every SM Entertainment fan knows.
In Korea, he is like the cornerstone of performance directing.
The best performance director.
(Starting with "Into the New World" by Girls' Generation)
(SHINee in 2008)
(EXO in 2012)
(Red Velvet in 2014)
(aespa in 2020)
(The choreographer who established the standard for SM's performances)
(The person who directs every single moment on stage)
(Performance Director Shim Jae Won)
He's worked as a performance director for a long.
I believe he will accurately evaluate...
the qualities and role of a director.
It felt reassuring.
- Jae Won! - Jae Won!
Did you know about this?
I had no idea.
(Sighing)
I thought I wouldn't be nervous.
But cold sweat was dripping down my spine.
Jae Won helped me tremendously in my growth.
He's a master who gave me...
so many teachings.
With Koo Young on my right...
and Jae Won sitting there judging us,
an overwhelming emotion suddenly rushed over me.
I wanted to prove myself with performances.
(Surprised)
The person who's meant to come is finally here.
(The third judge enters next.)
Anthony!
I really didn't expect him to come.
My name is Anthony,
representing the KINJAZ crew.
I'm also one of the creative directors.
He is someone leading the global trend of performance.
(The core creator of KINJAZ)
(For his unrivaled, world-class directing skills,)
(Anthony Lee is recognized globally as a world-renowned director.)
Being able to tell a story through my own piece was a huge opportunity.
I was so glad to see him because I love KINJAZ so much.
But I got nervous because I had to be evaluated.
They are all prominent figures in the scene.
I thought we had the rightful judges.
I'm going to get evaluated properly.
I think it started to hit me.
"It's really starting now."
In the 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission,
choreographers will be evaluated...
on how they reinterpreted the same signature choreography,
by assessing formations and compositions,
the utilization of main and supporting characters,
and the overall impact delivered on stage.
Only one winning choreographer from each matchup...
will leave their name on the Director Credit.
The 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
We will start the Last Run.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
Let's go!
My goal is to get my name up there as Director too.
The most important thing was to get my name on the Director Credit.
I have to get it up there, no matter what.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission, the 1st matchup)
We will now begin the Last Run for the Simeez versus Renan matchup.
Don't be nervous.
We have to do this.
We have to nail it.
Entering together like this made me so nervous.
The pressure was real.
But the look in my crew's eyes and their fierce drive...
gave me confidence,
which eased a lot of my nerves.
The dancers' energy gave me an extra boost of strength.
This feels like a Korea-Japan showdown.
I'm going to win for sure.
No one can beat me.
Team Simeez will enter first.
(Team Simeez)
(Team Renan)
Dancers, please move to the standing area.
(Team Simeez versus Team Renan, the dancers' entry is complete.)
Renan is the best!
- Renan is the best! - Renan is the best!
(Happy)
Having my dancers behind me...
gave me a boost of confidence without even realizing it.
- Renan is the best! - Simeez!
We are going to kill it.
We will now begin the Last Run for the Simeez versus Renan matchup.
Look at her costume.
(The 8 teams' green rooms are on air.)
Their outfits are so intense.
I bet Simeez is going to win.
She's just so overwhelming.
The impact is seriously strong.
(Overwhelming)
It's the toes for me. It's the shoes that make it crazy.
I paid attention all the way down to the shoes.
She painted her feet.
She came in with determination.
But...
Renan has so many original moves up her sleeve.
She's a director who excels so much at composition.
She is a dark horse.
I'll deliver an even greater impact through versatile formations.
The Last Run of the 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission,
Simeez versus Renan.
We will start with Renan's Last Run first!
(Simeez versus Renan, 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
My goodness!
It's starting now.
I'm so nervous.
We can do this.
It won't be easy for Renan...
to erase the original choreography of "Bang Bang."
The whole process was far from easy.
My pride and confidence hit rock bottom.
Simeez crafted the choreography so well.
I have to give credit where credit is due.
What winning factors do I even have?
Props? Concept?
There were none.
(Rehearsal D-1)
I have some unfortunate news.
We need a massive overhaul of "Bang Bang."
Yes. There will be major revisions.
I'm shocked as well.
It broke my heart.
What if it brings everyone down?
We were confident, thinking that...
we were cool and we would win.
My heart felt so heavy.
Please go to your initial positions...
- for "Bang Bang." - The initial positions.
It starts like this.
I needed to try a different vibe, which is bigger and more powerful.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
I'm sorry. We need to take this out.
- Forget about it. - Okay.
I was hitting a wall right from the start.
Could we make the front row into a horizontal line like this?
With JAYME in the center.
I see.
I'm sorry. This isn't it.
Can we try this move right here?
Or can you try raising your arms?
One, two.
Can you try it while standing up?
Hang on a second.
Her energy wasn't going up. She was being sensitive.
It feels like our energy is draining.
My mind is checked out right now.
Time is running out, but my brain just won't work.
I can see the dancers getting exhausted.
This isn't easy.
Can we take a quick five-minute break?
I'm sorry. Wait a moment.
We're ruined.
We're in trouble.
(In the end, she bursts into tears.)
Tears started flowing before I even realized it.
I was so heartbroken and overwhelmed.
I kept pretending to be fine...
and tried my hardest not to show it.
I worked really hard.
As bad results kept repeating,
my mental state was shattered,
and I felt like giving up.
Is she going to be okay?
(The practice room remains frozen in place.)
(Walking on eggshells)
Shall we keep working on the poses like this?
How about working on the poses?
We can do this. Something like this.
It's not that hard, is it?
- Like this. - Make it.
It would be beautiful if you make it a little better.
- You got this. - Great.
That's when I came to my senses.
I'm the director.
There's a performance I'm in charge of,
and there are dancers under my wing,
so I can't give up like this.
Because I've got the teammates who got my back,
I have to try everything I can.
I apologize for the major change.
But it's all for a good result.
- Let's do it! - Let's go!
(Our team's the best!)
It had to be easy enough for them to learn in a day,
and the moves had to be clear.
And the dancers had to shine.
I sized up the team.
I fixed the moves to be as flashy as possible...
and made the movements bigger.
JAYME will do some voguing in his part.
I changed the choreography to utilize each dancer's strength.
(The quality improves as she fixes the choreography one at a time.)
Seeing everyone happy made me happy.
I'm glad I made the changes.
If they see the changes I've made in a day,
they will say I'm mad.
Team Renan will enter now.
Now I just need to make sure...
- everything goes smoothly on site. - Okay.
Renan.
I've seen her a couple of times when working with aespa.
I remember her as someone who's good at composition.
It's fascinating to see the process.
She must be shocked...
that we are watching the rehearsal.
You have an hour and 20 minutes to rehearse.
(The 1-hour-and-20-minute rehearsal countdown begins.)
Who's going up to the second floor?
Should we check the path?
Yes!
She's got JAYME.
I guess JAYME appears from the second floor.
If she's using the second floor, time will be very tight.
- She has to check the distance too. - Right.
It's quite a distance, so she should consider the timing.
It's very hard.
Let's dance to the music.
Okay.
She's watching from the judges' point of view.
She is aware of...
who she's showing it to.
That's what's great.
It seems she's got the habit of looking at the big picture.
- There goes JAYME. - Yes.
That must be the spot.
Let's see.
Goodness.
(Flustered)
- He missed the timing. - That's just too far.
JAYME, it's too tough to go to the second floor, isn't it?
- I didn't make it. - Right?
(After the dance break on the floor,)
(he had 13 seconds to travel.)
Gosh, too far!
(When is he coming?)
Goodness, this won't work!
This won't work!
It's hard to use the second floor.
You need to lose it if it's not going to work.
Instead of going to the back, can I go this way?
You can.
(He uses the front stairs instead.)
(Sprinting)
Please, please.
(In the dark, JAYME runs up the stairs.)
Let's see.
(Fully locked in)
This has to work out.
(He appears.)
He had enough time.
(After two tries, he got the timing perfectly.)
(Relieved)
Thank you.
What she did well was addressing the problems quickly.
- They rehearsed well. - They did.
It will improve the quality of the performance.
No matter what happens, we did our very best.
Let's show them that.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Go, Team Renan!)
- Goodness. JAYME! - JAYME!
What is he going to do?
There are lots of moves JAYME can do.
She will need to come up with a good strategy.
The quality of the performance...
greatly depends on the director. I will show them that.
As a director, I can win no matter what.
- Today, everyone is... - Very serious.
All the time we spent working hard won't betray us.
Let's show them.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
I can already feel Renan's dark energy.
I'm curious about what Renan will show us.
Ready, fight.
Renan might just crush it.
(Dawn: From Dystopia to Utopia)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Armageddon": Simeez)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "BANG BANG": Simeez)
The intro is strong.
It's the first pose of "Armageddon."
- It's strong. - What's this?
What?
That's crazy.
They're walking on their knees. It's crazy.
That's...
Wow.
That's mad.
The intro is really tight. It keeps you locked in.
(Getting...)
(absorbed)
- I'm so excited. - Let's go.
It's straight up "Salmokji: Whispering Water."
They are like a warrior tribe.
(Gosh!)
She chose that dancer in the center cleverly.
(Amazing)
- Overall, it's well-designed. - Right.
I love its composition.
There she goes.
(Simeez's signature choreography part in "Armageddon")
I didn't feel nervous.
There she goes.
Renan has more impact than I expected.
She's determined.
It seems like she really didn't want to lose.
(Shocked)
I thought it was slow motion.
This slow-motion action is incredible.
And the formations are really well designed for a mega crew.
(Amazing)
It's crazy.
Didn't she do a good job here?
She made great use of space and levels.
I haven't seen a true mega crew stage like this for a while.
(Their jaws drop.)
- There he is. - He's here.
It's crazy.
JAYME!
Go!
- Yes, JAYME! - Let's go!
(Cheering)
(Simeez's signature choreography part in "BANG BANG")
She gave JAYME all the signature moves.
All the energy gets drawn to the center.
That's why he stands out.
She utilized the dancer well.
JAYME is ridiculously good.
What?
That's straight up "BANG BANG."
They’ve got all the heavy hitters in one place.
She really took it up a notch.
JAYME is too good.
JAYME!
Let's go!
Let's go, BIGGY!
Goodness.
Why is she so cool?
(What's this?)
When did JAYME get up there?
Did he take the elevator?
What?
His character is insane.
I think she was clever to change it.
It's well-developed.
It got much cooler than before.
I got nervous.
Let's go, JAYME!
(Surprised)
They went all in on sheer presence.
It's insane.
Renan is good.
Amazing!
She might win.
(Team Renan Dancers)
(BIGGY, JAYME, Emily, Pitu,)
(Maria, Ryuki, Sera and more)
That was crazy.
The knee-walking was mad.
(Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta)
Choosing JAYME was clever.
It was completely different from the rehearsal.
It's ridiculous.
- Its quality is very different. - Yes.
Very different. Yes.
That felt cathartic.
The great response made...
all that work of redesigning "BANG BANG" worth it.
She had made a lot of changes.
I came in fully prepared too.
I will pull it off perfectly.
Bring the platform. Where is the platform?
- Where's the platform? - The platform is here.
Let's bring the platform first.
My work involves a big object.
(Surprised)
She got ambitious.
When you use something like that, it gets predictable.
I'm curious to see how she will use it.
They're very good at creating the looks.
They care greatly about the looks.
- It will give them a good position. - If...
they express it through the style, it might be better.
We tried to keep the stylishness of "Avatar."
To match the character Varang.
You can color it in a straight line like this.
Like I said earlier, you need to draw a cross...
on the neck with red paint.
Do we paint our necks too?
- It would be nice if you do. - Okay.
We will go with blue then.
The dancers who belong to the water tribe are wearing blue.
All the other dancers...
will paint their bodies in red.
The last touch...
really changes the quality of the performance.
We have to win.
Losing isn't an option for me.
- What's that? - What's that?
That's incredible.
Even if you use a prop,
you need to use it well.
But do they really need it? There's risk.
It will shock you.
I guess they were surprised by how much we prepared.
I am confident.
I'm excited.
If they utilize the object well,
they will produce a grand scene.
They need to do better than they did yesterday.
What do you think will happen?
It depends on how Simeez does it.
I'm so curious. I hope they are strong too.
I wanted to show everyone everything we prepared.
Simeez will take the Director Credit.
It won't happen.
I need to win the Director Credit.
Ready, fight.
(The Armageddon War)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Armageddon": Simeez)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "BANG BANG": Simeez)
(Inspired by "Avatar: Fire and Ash")
(Performance by Team Simeez)
- Wow, holy. - Oh, gosh. What is it?
(Crazy intro)
That's crazy.
She's amazing.
Simeez, you are truly great.
- It's the first scene of "Avatar." - Right.
She went all in.
It was so shocking that I was a little worried.
It's as if she came out of the movie.
I got goosebumps.
I want our stage...
to leave a lasting impression.
(Simeez's signature choreography part in "Armageddon")
Nice.
They're scary.
This is a legendary performance.
It's the sword dance.
Just look at that.
Seriously, what can't she do?
Gosh.
Goodness.
Renan must be very frustrated.
I feel like she's going to beat us to death.
(Loving it)
They copied our shouting.
Must be the water tribe.
Rivalry?
It's Rian!
She's here.
Waackxxxy and Spella?
Let's go.
(Simeez's signature choreography part in "Bang Bang")
Waackxxxy!
No wonder the energy was exploding.
Let's go!
Oh, my goodness.
(100 percent absorbed)
She's a genius.
- Punch Bunny! - Punch Bunny!
Oh?
She appeared for a second.
I would've utilized her a little more.
Crazy.
Her movement is sensual,
so there are a lot of really captivating moves.
(In love with Simeez)
She's the exact opposite of me.
- Yes! - Yes!
She's really good at these things.
Let's go, Simeez!
I can feel the aura from Simeez.
- Goodness. - She's good at hitting the beats.
It was just like "Avatar."
Well done!
They killed it!
She's crazy.
(Watch the comparison video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
We did really well.
We had good teamwork.
It was flashy,
but I feel like it lacked dance moves.
Is it already over?
It was a show.
They had lots of highlights too.
As for me, it made me...
realize once again how passionate...
Simeez really is.
It's knee-walking versus...
mirror standing.
Yo.
- That was difficult for me. - It's so difficult.
- Yes, that was difficult. - Different styles.
I thought they would be surprised to see our performance.
I thought my performance had the power to win them over.
We did everything we could,
and we gave it our best.
What would the judges think?
(What would the judges say about the two choreographers?)
You two ladies, this is going to be a difficult one.
Simeez, what was good in your show...
was weak in Renan's show.
And what was good in your show was weak in her show.
That makes it complicated, and that makes it fun at the same time.
So it just depends on what we're going to put value in today.
(Agreeing)
(What's the judges' choice?)
I think Renan's show was just better...
and there was a more mature offering of movement.
I think there was more uniqueness. I think it started off strong.
(Renan's intro captured attention from the start.)
As each phrase built, the way they unleashed...
more and more energy...
looked incredible.
They created such a powerful stage picture...
that it made me want to be up there with them.
It made me realize that the energy I wanted to convey...
really came across.
Here's my impression of Simeez's performance.
I thought the intro was impactful enough...
to make me think of a Las Vegas show.
She drew inspiration from the Avatar characters,
introducing the Fire Tribe and the Water Tribe...
and setting up a clear conflict between them.
I thought it was a very intuitive and effective way to stage it.
How did she think of pulling off a concept like this...
in such a short given time?
She's got some serious guts.
She chose the lift a female dancer would usually avoid.
She chose an object that's too big to handle.
I think she constantly wants to break something.
Seeing her creating what she wants to do...
and continuing to challenge herself,
I admire her.
I believe it's the virtue a choreographer must possess.
I was very grateful to her for recognizing the challenge I took on.
It made me realize that my decision was right.
Ten years from now,
if you ask me to describe your show,
I will be able to describe your show easily.
I also gave a lot of points in props which were memorable.
The judges praised Simeez's performance.
I wasn't sure what was going to happen.
I think it boils down to the difference in energy.
- Difference in energy. - Yes.
Who do you think will win?
Raise your hand if it's Simeez.
Raise your hand if it's Renan.
It's hard to tell.
Here's what I don't understand.
There was still room for improvement.
Yes, she's a dancer with quality.
But she was abandoned after just one use.
I believe it's the director's role...
- to lead the team stably. - Yes.
But when we consider the result,
it would've been better if her show had had something...
that was strong enough to overwhelm us.
It would've been good if she had been bold enough...
to take the risk of taking a different path.
Actually, that's what's fun.
I feel like it's a little cheesy.
I just don't think she did it well enough.
- Right. - Right.
Why is the meeting getting longer?
I have to win here.
It would be devastating if I can't perform...
in front of an audience.
They put their trust in me and followed my lead.
I was worried that my conviction might have been wrong.
1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
Who will be able to showcase her work to the audience...
and put her name on the Credit Board?
(Hands held tightly together)
(It has to be us.)
The choreographer whose name will go on the Credit Board is...
Renan showcased a variety of things.
Renan did such a good job.
In terms of development and flow, Simeez did better.
It's...
I have to win.
It has to be my name.
The director?
It has to be Simeez.
It's...
(To be continued)
1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
Who will be able to showcase her work to the audience...
and put her name on the Credit Board?
(Hands held tightly together)
(It has to be us.)
It's...
I have to win.
It has to be my name.
The director?
It has to be Simeez.
It's...
(Renan wins.)
It's Renan.
(Renan put her name on the Director Credit.)
(Walking on his knees)
(The result shocks everyone.)
My name, "Renan" was on the screen.
I thought I was dreaming.
I was thrilled beyond words.
I was so happy.
(Feeling sorry)
(Team Renan's dancers enjoy the victory with her.)
Thank you.
In terms of utilizing dancers,
Renan's choice...
hit home for me.
I agree with what she said about the dancer utilization.
The way that she should've debut Waackxxxy...
It should've been a blowup.
- That's right. - Yes.
But she kind of just walks forward, and she's not in the center.
And you're like, is there...
I agree wholeheartedly.
JAYME? Seeing him up there, the way that he...
The way he walks in front, I'm like,
that's a blowup. That's a powerful way to have...
It's not even just dancer utilization.
It's the setup, the formation, the transition.
(She agrees.)
The charm of JAYME...
was expressed very well.
I really liked how you used the second floor.
I was deeply moved by that.
It was worth redoing the whole "BANG BANG" part.
Choreographer Renan.
You became the director of the first mission,
and you'll be able to showcase your performance to the audience.
Last night, I prayed for a miracle...
before I went to bed.
I changed the choreography over and over again,
and it gave me the chance to grow.
I'd like to thank everyone who gave me such a good opportunity.
Thank you.
(You're so cool, Director Renan!)
Actually, losing wasn't an option, so I'm...
- You did well. - Yes.
(You're the best, Simeez.)
I'm just glad I was able to work with all of them.
Thank you so much.
I love you!
I did take over the signature choreography,
and I didn't expect to lose.
I'm sad that my name didn't go up on the Credit Board as the director.
- Captain! - Good job.
- You're cool. - You're cool.
Good job.
The only choreographer...
who successfully left her name on this stage...
was Renan.
Renan, please prepare your performance.
- Thank you. - You worked hard.
Thank you.
(The battle between the two heated rivals...)
(ends with Renan's victory.)
- Good job. - Good job.
Good job.
- You did so well. - You're the best.
Don't cry. You did so well.
- My gosh. - You were so cool.
I must've made too many risky moves.
No, you didn't.
It's just a matter of preference.
I wanted to make something that would bridge the gap.
- You did well. - That's not true.
You'd feel very upset.
No. We were cool.
I'm so sorry.
I said we wouldn't lose.
I thought we wouldn't lose.
(She's sorry she didn't win them the victory as promised.)
- I'm sorry. - No, we're okay.
It got me thinking that I was doing something wrong.
I felt bad for the dancers.
Simeez the best director.
Thank you so much.
Seriously, thank you so much.
They were comforting me.
It was so touching.
(It was so touching.)
(If I lose, I'll die.)
(The conflict with the dancers arise.)
(You're being annoying.)
(I've said this 10 times.)
(Everyone is running the same way except you.)
(We need to practice the group dance more.)
(We have a time limit.)
(Was my team very inefficient?)
(Why won't you say this...)
(when I ask if there's any problem?)
(I told you to check things like this.)
(Am I...)
(too overbearing?)
(I don't know if they have that big impact.)
(If I lose, with the kind of personality I have,)
(I can't leave.)
(Which 5 performances will they get to showcase to the audience?)
(1st day of practice)
You're doing well.
(Team BADA is practicing.)
(And so is Team INGYOO.)
(All the teams are busy practicing.)
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Lift it up.
What is happening?
I'm screwed. Did I join the wrong team?
We don't have much time.
I got all the performances as I'd planned.
(This is his planned performance?)
Because in my performance,
I'm the main character.
(Back Koo Young's concept sheet is full of "I.")
I'm making full use of myself.
You need the main character to lead the story,
and I'm confident as a dancer too.
I need to do a perfect performance in just six days.
Can I make 40 Back Koo Youngs? No.
In a large-group performance, instead of their unique characters,
it's important to make the overall picture look nice...
by working together.
So rather than giving characters to the dancers,
I decided to use them as an element of the whole picture.
The keyword is...
"Back Koo Young's inside."
(Back Koo Young's inside?)
You are my cells.
(I am Back Koo Young's cell?)
- Some will swim, - Two, three, four.
some will lift others,
and some will do the scorpion pose.
I had it planned long ago.
That's why I let Kasper choose first.
About him taking those five dancers,
it didn't mean much to me.
As long as my dancers have a strong foundation,
I'll have no issue with directing them.
(During the casting session,)
(Back Koo Young tested them on the basic moves.)
- He's really doing that. - Five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two. - What you must practice the most...
is the basic, fundamental movements.
That leads to your skills.
(This is why...)
(he chose based on the basic moves only.)
But that aside,
more than anything, teamwork is most important.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
(He brings up the excitement with a cheer before the practice starts.)
Since a lot of them are inexperienced,
I wanted to give them confidence...
that they can do well.
(Confidence up!)
Everyone is working hard,
and I don't want them to get hurt.
I emphasized a lot on the dancers' conditions.
(Back Koo Young's dancers have gathered in one corner.)
(And a mysterious box)
(They're knee pads.)
(Back Koo Young's flex for the 40 hardworking dancers)
(You're awesome, Koo Young!)
A lot of performances require them...
to kneel.
It really hurts if you practice those moves...
without any protective gear.
Are you wearing the knee pads?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Are you wearing the knee pads? - Yes.
We need to be injury-free to practice together.
It helps with the quality of the work as well.
Enabling the dancers...
to dance as freely as they can...
is a director's job as well.
Now, I need to do well.
As a director, of course,
but I want to do my part as a dancer as well.
I run, dance, and run again.
It will be exhausting. It's very exhausting.
But I should do it since it's my choreography.
I dance as the main character,
and the dancers come together to form a scenery.
That way, I'm sure I can make a good performance...
without many outstanding dancers.
I don't agree.
I hate using them as random Dancer 1, Dancer 2.
They shouldn't just act as backup dancers.
They should become a scene...
and make a story. I think they have important roles.
So I gave them characters.
(Kasper, the true self who tries to maintain the inner peace)
In the concept I came up with,
I'll depict the "me" that I want to show others.
Shuri is my evil self.
The dancers are evil energy.
(Evil energy?)
And the bosses of the evil energy, the four kings.
(We're the four kings?)
By giving them character,
it helps them to get immersed more.
It gives them responsibilities too.
We must win no matter what.
If we lose,
this performance will be gone.
Since we came here, we must perform on stage.
Exactly.
Shuri.
Three from Penrose.
Nino.
Their dancing and vibe...
It's of the highest caliber.
The first important part...
will be performed by dancers from Penrose.
Shuri and Nino will dance powerfully...
and give off the strong energy.
For the highlight, where it needs to explode,
Shuri and I will give off the energy.
How is it?
(Thumbs up!)
(Feeling proud)
"It's impossible for me to lose." Or so I thought.
But things don't always go according to plan.
Number 1, Number 2.
Again.
Again. You're slow.
(Me?)
It wasn't a difficult part,
but she couldn't do it.
To be honest, I was frustrated.
Again.
(Dancer Noura keeps making the same mistake.)
Hold on.
Let's focus, shall we?
(Noura holds the group back by making the same mistake.)
(Glancing)
(Frustrated)
Some may do their best in every given moment,
but some may not.
There's a villain in the team.
Everyone is talking about the same person.
We need to do something about Noura.
We got off on the wrong foot.
- Alexandra. - Here.
(They started the first day practice in an upbeat mood.)
Noura?
(Looking around)
Noura isn't here.
She was late to the first practice.
I already know she's not the best dancer.
The formation too...
(During "Love Shot" formation practice)
- And go this way. - Why?
Move to the right.
(She runs in between them!)
Noura. Don't stay there. Move immediately.
Penrose members need to walk to the front,
and she's still running across.
If she can't do it,
she should come in early to practice or something.
But she keeps checking herself in the mirror and brushing her hair.
It's the problem of attitude and will.
That got me angrier.
Whether your role is big or small, in front or behind,
you need to do your part...
for this to become perfect.
Think of this as your own stage.
We're all working together to make this performance.
I hope you'll focus.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's dance to the song.
(Keeping an eye on her)
(Noura makes the same mistake again.)
(What is it?)
When is your timing?
(Noura can't answer.)
I was at a loss for words.
If your mistake is holding everyone back,
you should work harder.
I have no intention to lose,
but at this rate, I might actually lose.
Koo Young and Kasper.
I can't wait to watch them.
Okay. Let's go, Koo Young.
I wonder what he did.
Let's see how impressive it is.
(Back Koo Young's choreography practice)
My gosh.
(Everyone is surprised at the extraordinary intro.)
I like this choreography.
How did he train the dancers with this technique?
Goodness.
His moves are similar to mine.
He really made full use of himself.
Koo Young is so passionate.
He meant it when he wrote "making full use of Back Koo Young."
All I can remember is him running.
He keeps running.
(He keeps running.)
Make full use of Back Koo Young.
The chorus is in perfect sync.
The perfect sync gives stability.
(How did Kasper react to Back Koo Young's performance?)
(Having mixed feelings)
Okay.
I felt very worried.
Koo Young is watching mine.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so curious.
I'll watch reverently.
(Changing her seating position)
My gosh.
Nice.
I like that mirroring.
(Back Koo Young watches Kasper's video closely.)
(He's smiling?)
(The dancers are not in sync.)
(Oh, dear.)
I don't know.
It's so disappointing.
I get what they're doing,
and he has a lot of choreography and formations,
but the dancers are not ready.
They only have one day left, but this...
I don't think they can pull it off on the stage.
I can't face Kasper if I beat him in this too.
(Gosh, Kasper...)
(Back Koo Young is voted as the expected director.)
(Did you see that, Kasper?)
(I won again!)
The expected director is Koo Young?
(He became even more concerned with the result.)
What should I do?
(The votes were 7 to 1 for Back Koo Young.)
The dancers aren't ready.
Kasper's performance has a risk.
It is affected way too much by the dancers' skills.
I'm so grateful for my dancers once again.
(He stares at the expected Credit Board for a long time.)
How should I overcome...
this hurdle?
I'm at a loss.
(Kasper becomes more worried. How will the match go?)
Hello!
Come in, everyone.
They're starting smoothly and immediately.
It's funny how I'm judging them.
(Their direct senior is watching them.)
You of all people are here.
How long have you worked with Koo Young and Kasper?
More than 20 years.
I've seen them since they were a novice.
(Laughing)
They'll do well.
Does the countdown start now?
The 1-hour-20-minute countdown starts now.
Okay. Dancers, have your free time.
(Free time?)
See you later.
(Back Koo Young goes somewhere, leaving the dancers behind.)
As soon as I went in, I said bye to the dancers.
I told them to do as they liked for 5 to 10 minutes.
Check the backstage...
and go up the second floor for those who'll be going there.
A lot of my dancers have little experience being on stage.
So I taught them how to check the blocking...
on stage.
I made the rule for moving in the backstage.
If you're going to the front, walk inside.
If you're going to the back, walk outside.
So your paths don't cross.
The light fixtures, the staff members' chairs,
the cameras they're not using.
You could find these stuff there.
You need to check those out and block based on that.
You must remember this...
to use the 80 minutes effectively tomorrow.
- Okay. - Okay.
Where's the stage manager?
I want to check the lighting.
I'm going to find the stage manager as soon as I go in...
to check the lighting.
Can I check the lighting for each scene?
- That's good. - He gives off the veteran vibe.
I'll discuss the lighting cues with the stage manager,
and once it's done, we'll check it over...
with the music.
Ten minutes have passed.
I'll join as a dancer to rehearse.
He's joining them.
- He should check first. - Exactly.
He should check overall.
(The first rehearsal starts with Back Koo Young's technique.)
(The dancers need to enter from the backstage.)
Gosh, stay focused.
- Oh, dear. - My gosh.
What to do with them?
Goodness.
You can't see that when you're on stage yourself.
(The first blocking rehearsal ends like that.)
Is there any problem so far?
(Me!)
I couldn't make it in time.
It was too far, so I exited this way.
- Did you check the backstage? - Yes.
- Did you run? - Yes.
Try it again.
Try using the backstage corridor.
You should have enough time to make it.
Koo Young is both a dancer and a director.
He can't switch the mode quickly enough.
(He couldn't spot the blocking issue at the back because he was dancing.)
Because he's playing two roles at the same time.
The clash happens from being a dancer and a director...
at the same time.
Let's try it again.
(After the initial technique,)
(he runs out of the stage.)
He stepped out.
He should check the overall performance.
He's checking the overall stage now.
What was that?
(The dancers moving toward the same direction collided.)
(What was that?)
That kind of mistake makes you angry.
- Their timing is off. - They're not in sync.
(His face slowly hardens from the mistakes.)
(The problematic part)
(His eyes are moving fast.)
(The back-right dancers come in late again.)
(He spots them.)
Why is this happening?
What went wrong?
Who couldn't make it?
Are you guys running?
Or did you guys stop over there?
We just stopped right there.
Why did you stop over there?
Hyun Seo needs to go to the front,
so we stop for a while and wait until she passes.
Why would you stop there?
You can stop here.
You can come here and wait.
Why do you think I gave you ten minutes...
to check the backstage?
So you can check stuff like this.
I got sensitive.
In the practice room,
I taught them how to check the timing...
for running backstage, and we practiced it as well.
There are five entrances.
Two on the left,
two on the right,
and one in the middle.
They're all on the first floor.
You need to come in like this.
Do you get it? Understand?
You must walk in between the blue tapes.
You need to calculate the speed of running.
Even on the site,
I gave them time to check the backstage,
but the problem still arose,
which made me become sensitive.
Do I need to tell you every single thing?
I gave you time to check so I don't need to do that.
Don't do that.
Who went in late just now? I saw you too.
Think. Is this actually a problem?
Is it really impossible to make it on time when you run?
If yes, I'll change it.
- He's angry. - If yes, I'll change it.
- Understandable. - You have no willpower.
Understandable.
- Can you run and make it? - Yes.
- Then do it. You must make it work. - Okay.
- Make it work. - Okay.
When you have limited time for the rehearsal,
you can't help but become sensitive.
Acting sensitive and making the performance successful...
- It's better. - is definitely better.
What wasn't an issue in the practice room...
became an issue on stage.
We need to go back to the practice room...
and go over every detail again.
(Right after the blocking rehearsal, they're back in the practice room.)
We'll do it slowly from the start.
(Fine-tuning the details)
We checked each and every detail again.
Eleni, you were fast.
(Fast Eleni admits fast.)
You can't make a mistake with something like this.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Perfectly in sync)
You must practice perfectly before performing on stage.
I'll make it work until the end.
(Back Koo Young versus Kasper)
- We'll do a warm-up together. - One, two, three.
Five, six.
Don't mind what others do. Focus on yourself.
He must've given it his all,
but so did we.
I can show them the difference.
The difference?
The class?
We're in different classes.
I think he's in middle class.
We're in super heavy class.
- Gosh, Koo Young. - Hello.
- He's wearing white. - Out of all colors.
You look cool.
(The dancers enter the stage.)
We'll kill them.
This is going to be so fun. I can't wait.
I'm not nervous at all.
We'll do great.
Yes. Let's do this.
Let's do this.
He's handsome.
(He's handsome.)
You're handsome!
(They finally meet on stage.)
They must be nervous.
My gosh.
I'm nervous.
Koo Young. You've watched each other's rehearsal.
What's one thing that worries you the most?
About his performance, you mean?
Just now,
instead of watching his performance, I closed my eyes...
and ran a simulation in my head as I listened to the music.
(During Team Kasper's dress rehearsal)
We get to watch each other's rehearsal.
It's another chance to run through my own...
as I listen to the music while he performs.
(Anthony Lee laughs.)
He's sick. Sick and smart.
I was confident I'd win,
so I wasn't annoyed by him.
I wanted to show him.
I'll crush him.
1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission, Last Run.
We'll check out Back Koo Young's performance first.
Back Koo Young and his dancers, please get ready to perform.
- Let's do this. - Good luck.
Let's have fun.
My dancers are much more in sync.
I'm confident that I made a better performance.
That's why I must win.
I know Koo Young will put up an amazing performance.
So I was worried.
That's a cool start.
Ready, fight.
I'm excited.
Let's go, Koo Young.
Let's go.
("Trace" by Back Koo Young)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Guilty": Back Koo Young)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Love Shot": Back Koo Young)
(Depiction of the internal turmoil of Back Koo Young)
(Performance by Team Back Koo Young)
The choreography requires a difficult technique.
Hey!
Oh, my gosh. They're doing the backstroke.
It feels great, Koo Young.
That's amazing.
Yes!
That's insane.
Gosh, the expression is insane.
The density of the moves feels different.
Gosh, I want to see this up close.
Gosh!
They're all in sync.
The judges had great reactions.
(Back Koo Young's signature choreography part in "Guilty")
Why is he so sexy?
Yes!
- That's insane. - That's so impressive.
Gosh, that was done in sync.
The formation looks nice.
(Clearing his sight)
How are they this good together?
(Impressed)
Sexy guy!
The choreography itself is so good.
They're really moving as one.
- How is it this neat? - He's amazing.
- Let's go! - There she is!
It's no:ze!
She's so pretty.
Gosh, it's so neat.
Gosh, he won't stop running.
(Back Koo Young's signature choreography part in "Love Shot")
"Love Shot!"
This is the goosebump point!
- Let's go, no:ze! - Oh, my gosh!
She has a great presence.
What? He went up.
- I love the presentation. - Right.
Okay! Take it off!
- Gosh! - Nice!
They're so good.
- Gosh, they did a great job. - Right.
- How are they so good together? - They must've practiced so hard.
He definitely disappeared just now. How did he come out from there?
This is a magic show.
- He's running again. - He won't stop running.
Macho!
Gosh, there you go! They're so good!
- They're moving as one. - Yes!
- The formation is perfect. - They're so good.
There we go.
Gosh, it's so neat.
They keep running.
Yes!
(Team Back Koo Young's dancers)
- I got goosebumps. - Gosh.
(no:ze, Kevin Choi, Mun Kyeong, Yoon Ji and more)
"Love Shot!"
(Amazed)
There's something new every three seconds.
That's insane.
He ground his teeth.
What a great ending. I love that.
Nice.
Koo Young was really neat.
He must feel so nervous about having to dance...
after watching that.
Gosh, Kasper must feel so nervous right now.
My breathing got heavier,
but I was determined to win.
Hello.
- Great work, Koo Young. - Hey, Kasper.
- Good luck. - Thank you.
- Great work. - Thank you.
You're sweating.
- You should've slacked off. - Good luck.
You should've slacked off.
All right, everyone. Gather up.
- Okay. - Okay.
They're starting. Their session has begun.
- It has begun. - All right.
Please mark the positions.
- We'll do a number check. - Okay.
Please check the numbers.
Could we check the lights first?
That's wise.
While taking the lead,
he asked the others to take control of the field.
If this supportive structure isn't formed,
it's really hard to lead the group.
With the spotlight on, I want the mood to be dark.
- The surroundings will be darker. - Right.
This is how it should be done. You must work with the lights.
For a technical rehearsal,
the lights must come first.
The lights must be seen first for the cameras to catch up.
The lights must be accurate...
for the work you want to express to be displayed clearly.
That's how the cameras will capture that.
My priorities for this rehearsal...
are the blackout timing, silhouette lights, and spotlight.
I always focus a lot on the lights.
During "The Jennifer Hudson Show,"
I was in the lighting room...
when he performed "Long Way Home."
I want to battle it out with those details.
I'm certain that performances using lights...
will shine brighter on the stage.
Can we see what the complete blackout is like?
Let's check the complete blackout.
Can the dancers turn on the lights?
Okay. Let's check the first formation.
I have a bad feeling about this.
When using objects like those, it must be completely dark.
Then, they won't be able to see.
That can become a risk.
(They try the flashlight part during the blackout.)
- Can you see? - I can't see at all.
- The center is right here. - No. This won't work.
This won't work.
They had to be in formation during the blackout,
but they couldn't, as they weren't able to see.
We'll stop here.
It's hard to see where we are.
Dancers, can you see the marks?
- It's hard to see. - It's hard to see?
How do the silhouette lights sound?
The formation had to be neat.
The prism colors are seen with the silhouette lights,
creating a unique vibe.
The silhouette lights were only used...
right before the flashlight part.
I think this will work.
Was the glitch effect used on purpose?
He did a really good job.
He's very quick to adapt.
He provides a solution right away.
- Those lights look nice. - Right.
Kasper moves differently with the lights.
The lights determine...
the angles of the performance.
As Kasper has experience with concerts,
he knows how important the lights are.
How many minutes do we have left, Shuri?
- We have 59 minutes left. - We have 59 minutes left.
Shall we try that part?
- Yes. - Yes.
(During the transition section...)
(when the Penrose members move forward,)
(one dancer is late to move out.)
Noura made a mistake again.
The Penrose members had to move forward,
but she kept getting in the way on her own.
That kept causing a problem with the movement.
(During every "Love Shot" practice session,)
(Noura kept forgetting her line and position.)
(Move right here.)
Noura.
(Move to the right!)
(Running right through the middle)
(Noura!)
(Don't stay there. Move immediately.)
We already knew she lacked skill.
(Again. You're slow.)
(Noura keeps making mistakes with the moves and timing.)
Noura! Why are you moving out late?
You have to be faster to move away.
You have to think it'll be death if you don't move away.
It ruins the formation for the next part.
(They keep trying that part.)
Boom, two, three, four,
- Are you listening to the song? - five, six, seven, eight.
(Sighing)
Hold on. I'll take that part.
(Kasper ends up going down to take Noura's part.)
(Feeling nervous)
I want to know why Kasper is going down.
- He called out someone's name. - I see.
She'll be trembling right now.
Make the formation for the outro of "Love Shot."
(Moving in perfect order)
Did you two keep getting into each other?
We got into each other when I moved this way.
But she moved behind me just now.
Move out.
Play the song...
at around 1 minute and 15 seconds.
This is a mindset problem in the end.
"It won't work."
But you haven't tried everything you could.
(He tries that part instead of Noura.)
(Kasper moves away without any problems.)
It works. I saw it with my own eyes.
But she kept saying it wouldn't work.
I got away right away, didn't I?
If I move to that side at the last part...
It should be like this, but...
It's like that for everyone.
It's not just you. It's like that for everyone.
Right.
Just run out.
- Nothing is impossible, everyone. - Right.
You must not wander around.
Kasper is precise with his standards.
If a part doesn't match what he imagined,
he's the type to be harsh on his juniors.
He's someone...
who wants to express exactly what he imagined.
I believe that's positive to a certain extent.
I worked on the details of the lights and movement.
I felt anxious.
Get ready for the rehearsal.
- Okay. - Rehearsal.
Let's get into the intro formation quickly.
Make sure to hide your flashlights.
- Okay. - Okay.
You must not get it wrong.
(The dress rehearsal of Team Kasper begins.)
(However,)
(some of the flashlights can be seen.)
The lights looked so messy.
That looks quite messy.
(Shaking her head)
(Noura)
(During the problematic part,)
(Noura moves out late again.)
Gosh!
Noura! Why...
We won.
I thought that the quality of our performance...
was much better.
What was the problem?
Noura. You got in the way when you moved out.
I forgot again.
You have to move away as the others are coming in.
(The waiting room is silent after the dress rehearsal.)
Did you work on moving away, Noura?
I forgot. I'm sorry.
Are you going to constantly say...
you're sorry after messing up in the actual performance?
- I'll work harder. - That's not what's important.
Who won't work hard here?
It's important not to make a mistake today.
Where should you position yourself to move out perfectly?
I'll recover from my stress.
- What? - I'll recover...
- from my stress. - Right.
Rather than that...
- I'll do a better job. - Hey, keep quiet.
What was that?
I'll do a better job.
(Noura is about to shed tears.)
Don't cry.
Crying won't change anything.
(She ends up shedding tears.)
That's not it.
(Reading the room)
She made the same mistake even during the last rehearsal.
I was standing on the edge of a cliff.
A simple push would make me fall over.
It won't matter if I lose against something amazing.
But that isn't the case.
Right now,
I'm starting to think that we're going to lose.
The one who fails will continue to fail.
This is a matter of failing to concentrate.
"Oh, I made a mistake." This means nothing.
Between a dancer and director,
the dancer who gets the job done...
will be given another chance to work with me.
It's all up to you, not me.
"I will work hard." This won't mean anything to me.
Getting your job done is all you can do.
I can't lose.
I'm already at the edge of a cliff. One more wrong step...
will get me killed.
I'm confident.
I must win.
But I think this team can win.
The lights can change the game.
The dancers came out sweating buckets.
It's the fog!
It'll look great, right?
Gosh!
Let's hurry.
And now,
it's time for Kasper's Last Run.
Are you ready?
(He's ready.)
Ready, fight!
(Synopsis: Expression of mutual destruction...)
(of human duality and inevitable contradiction)
(Main characters: Kasper, ego that tries to maintain inner peace,)
(Shuri, the conflicting ego that destroys oneself)
(Performance by Team Kasper)
Gosh, check out the presentation.
He disappeared.
(Focused)
That's so impressive! Oh, my gosh!
The fog was well used.
He's filming a music video.
He went epic.
This one feels like a show with the movement of the lights.
It's like watching a concert.
Kasper is taking TAEMIN's role.
(Cheering)
- He made it eye-catching. - Right.
I believe our performance was more impressive.
(Back Koo Young's signature choreography part in "Guilty")
He has been possessed by TAEMIN.
It feels completely different.
This one makes you focus even more.
I like it.
I like this formation.
(Satisfied)
They're against each other.
It's the mirror image!
This seems like the signature part. It was planned out well.
There was a diagonal transition and it turned out well.
Shuri, the super dancer.
Someone has come inside Shuri.
Gosh, there you go, Shuri!
- Hey! - They worked hard with the lights.
He's using the lights really well.
I thought my team could be in danger.
(Screaming)
He's not an easy opponent. He won't go down.
He's flying around.
(Amazed by the lights)
The lights are insane.
(Back Koo Young's signature choreography part in "Love Shot")
He made it feel more like a fantasy.
Are they making an arrow for "Love Shot?"
They're the two suns.
This team used the lights really well.
So clean.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go, Penrose!
Come on, Penrose!
- Gosh, I'm a huge fan. - Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's go, Penrose!
Gosh, they're so good!
The pop can be seen from here.
He brought these three?
How can they dance like that?
They're such great dancers.
(Audience satisfaction: 100 percent)
Nino!
It feels like this team has more talented dancers.
Shuri is insane.
He's such a great dancer.
Let's go! Yes!
There we go.
It looks nice with the two tall ones.
That's insane.
Hold on. It's completely different from the rehearsal.
- That was great! - Awesome!
Nice!
(Watch the comparison video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
(Kasper's performance is over.)
The energy for the ending was great.
- Right. - The ending was great.
The lights were definitely captivating.
Right.
The lights were insane.
The lights were really important for this performance.
Yummy lights.
Do you know what's incredible?
I had Koo Young in my mind as the winner.
Has your mind changed?
I think it will.
I prefer Koo Young's performance.
There was something thrilling about it.
- This is a win by a landslide. - This one?
It's the opposite for me.
I'm not sure what the Judges will think about the lights.
It will be a headache for them.
I don't know what to expect.
Please come up to the stage, Back Koo Young.
Great job.
We will hear the evaluation...
on Back Koo Young's Last Run.
The whole show as a thing,
so much happened in the first half...
that I was kind of just like...
I will say that I didn't like...
transitioning like this...
or running like this.
(The transitions were done in a stooped posture.)
But I know you're more talented than that...
and I know where you're telling us to focus.
You just have to know that you're still...
You're always performing.
It feels very...
I dont know. College level?
Gosh.
I felt a chill down my spine.
He wasn't able to make a good start.
There's a gap.
I didn't feel anything crazy...
until the girl showed up in the middle...
and then feel something...
in the second half. That's what I got.
That girl showed up and I went, "Woah."
And then she ends up over there, and I'm like, "Wow!"
"This is great!" I even told them, "That was so cool!"
I was like, "That was so cool!" Amazing job.
(Satisfied)
While watching the rehearsal yesterday,
it felt like you were struggling as you tried to take care of...
many different things on your own. That was disappointing to see.
But with today's performance,
I believe you've done a lot with your own abilities.
With you as an experienced lead,
it was impressive how the performance was well-structered.
As the story was expressed well,
the meaning of the running made sense.
I was impressed by the expression of...
how the man and woman failed to meet each other.
Was there a significant reason...
for the music to be struck exactly on the beat?
Gosh, that's sharp.
There were quite a lot of dancers without any stage experience.
I didn't make the rhythm-making feel difficult.
I came up with a choreography that was on the beat...
and uniformized the dancers to be seen as one big chunk.
It was the process to bring up the quality as much as possible.
That point...
was right up my alley.
I noticed that you tried to fit the density of that energy...
in one beat.
I want to give you a big round of applause for the quality.
I felt so grateful that she noticed those things.
The Judges are so sharp.
Gosh, I never thought about losing.
I felt a rush of anxiety.
Gosh, I'm feeling nervous.
(What did they think about Kasper's Last Run?)
You're also a person who likes making challenges.
This was the challenge you made.
The objects you must have used many different times before...
were placed at an important part.
The expressions you wanted to make of the ego...
were clearly presented.
You understood many different types of lights.
You did well to use those lights...
in an effective way.
I learned a lot from you. Thank you.
I loved that you started small.
Especially because the stage is so big.
You took the lighting away. You took everything away.
Small dramatics. The smoke came in, and then all the dancers showed up.
It just took me into your world.
A lot of good things were said to me.
"I did it. I survived."
I've got to admit.
The first half was better than the second half.
"What? What's going on all of a sudden?"
You're making me feel like my heart is beating...
"Oh, my gosh! What's going to happen?"
And then, when the beat drops and the moment happens...
(The buildup phase)
It just doesn't make me explode...
the way you're making me feel the setup.
Your setups are so good.
You need to be able to pay it off right when you get to the top. Okay?
It made me wonder if I was going to lose again.
The moment I heard the evaluations from the judges,
I thought I was going to win.
I was certain that I was going to win.
When you compare the formation of their performances,
Kasper's performance was more varied.
But from a judge's perspective,
I'd say that this guy's performance made a greater impact.
- Sounds good. - Okay.
Let's do that.
Kasper definitely came up with better setups.
But wasn't his storyline a bit less clear than Koo Young's?
Koo Young's performance had a solid storyline.
But Kasper just had a high level of performance. Right?
Earlier in the 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission,
the choreographers faced off...
in the signature choreography takeover match.
Koo Young took the win,
and the song, "Guilty," went to Koo Young.
Will Koo Young be able to keep the momentum going...
and secure his spot on the Credit Board as a director?
It was my choreography.
I couldn't let him become the director.
Or will Kasper turn the tables...
and establish himself as a director?
I believe my name deserves to go to the board as the director.
We'll reveal it now.
- Yes! - Let's go!
- Oh, please. - This is making me nervous.
- Please. - I'm getting more nervous for him.
I think Kasper is going to win.
I'd say Koo Young's performance...
exploded with an wow factor.
It's neck and neck.
I have no idea how this is going to pan out.
I'll win for sure. It's impossible to lose with this performance.
I can definitely turn the tables around.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
What?
For real? Why?
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
(Kasper wins.)
- Yes! - Yes!
I heard people cheering.
(Cheering)
(Screaming)
There was a huge burst of cheering.
(Checking the results)
(Feeling proud)
I won.
(Koo Young checks the final results too.)
(Nodding)
(Well done.)
- Kasper! - Kasper!
It was a well-earned victory.
Well done. Great work.
- Yes! - Yes!
A wave of mixed feelings came over me.
- Kasper! - I was happy.
- But I was concerned about him too. - Kasper!
- Kasper! - Kasper!
- Kasper! - Kasper.
- Kasper! - How do you feel now?
(Kasper is having a hard time finding his words.)
My goodness.
(He bursts into tears he's been holding back.)
(Koo Young can't bring himself to look at Kasper who's crying now.)
To be honest, during this mission,
I felt like I was standing on the edge of a cliff.
I did all this to prove to people who the real director was.
(Fumbling)
(During the signature choreography takeover match,)
(he faced crisis after crisis.)
I lost with the score of 9 to 0.
My expected rank during the mid-point review...
(In disbelief)
I lost again with 7 to 1.
It made me wonder...
if I shouldn't have joined this show at all.
I thought...
I was doing a good job as a director.
But afterward, I kept doubting myself...
and thought I was wrong.
But now,
it feels like I finally got the validation...
that I was right. So I'm very grateful for that.
He handled this crisis really well.
I'm very happy right now.
I felt this way even before getting evaluated.
It didn't matter who won. Me or Kasper.
I knew I was going to be happy no matter what.
Now that it happened, I'm actually very happy for him.
This is odd, isn't it?
(During Kasper's performance)
Clap a lot when he finishes.
- Okay. - Okay.
As you saw, Kasper went through a lot...
to pull off this performance.
I could see how hard it was for him in his eyes.
I ended up rooting for Kasper before I realized it.
That's a cool way to end the performance.
I prayed with the others that he would finish strong.
So in a way, I'm happy it turned out this way.
Kasper got more confidence from this.
So I'm satisfied with it.
I was so happy.
I was incredibly happy to show Koo Young that I had improved.
I could feel that he was sincerely congratulating me.
I was so grateful.
Judging the two of you took a heavy emotional toll...
on me.
Actually, this is still taxing on me.
I know better than anyone...
how you guys grew as choreographers and about your struggles.
Watching you perform gave me a lot to think about.
But this is still a competition.
I tried my best to judge your performances objectively.
Both of you are outstanding dancers...
as performers and players in this competition.
Your dance skills are on par with each other.
However...
To me, I think it is this difference.
If this was a dance competition,
then I think this one wins.
- Right. - Please interpret.
You also got to understand...
you're not just talking to dancers. You're talking to the whole world.
So a non-dancer who watches this...
What are they going to be able to describe from this? So...
I feel the same way.
When I considered the fact that this would air all around the world,
not just in Korea,
I thought Kasper came up with...
more interesting setups that we hadn't seen before.
The utilization of the dancers...
was more dynamic and colorful. With that in mind,
I voted for Kasper.
(Thank you.)
In the end, the sole choreographer...
who successfully got his name on the Credit Board...
as a director was Kasper.
- Great job. - Say goodbye to your dancers.
(Shim Jae Won showers the choreographers with applause.)
(My team is the best!)
(I did it!)
- Kasper! - Kasper!
(You're such a crybaby)
(The crybaby is just happy.)
I felt bad that I might have hurt their feelings...
by being so blunt.
For some reason, I felt bad.
Of course, I was grateful.
(Enjoying the victory to the fullest)
Well done, no:ze.
Seriously. You did a great job.
You were great, Koo Young.
Great job, everyone.
- Good work. - Good work.
Of course, I'm disappointed. This is a competition.
I feel bad that we lost.
My dancers worked really hard.
I bet everyone got five bruises each.
They didn't have any stage experience,
and we met for the first time during this mission.
I honestly didn't expect them to keep up this well.
They worked hard...
to help me win.
I could totally feel their energy.
I was really touched.
We came behind in the judges' evaluation.
But what we can do is remember this process...
and we can hopefully meet again.
- Great job. - Good work!
(Thank you!)
Here you go. It's nothing big.
Thank you.
- Gosh, no. - Koo Young has handwritten letters.
(Koo Young wrote a letter by hand for every dancer...)
(to show his gratitude.)
I was really grateful that my dancers worked hard.
I wanted to express my gratitude.
I thanked everyone in the letters.
This is so sad.
If we ever get to work together again, I'll make us win.
(If we ever get to work together again, I'll make us win.)
(They're on the verge of tears.)
My goodness. What is this?
- Great job, Koo Young. - Thank you.
- Thank you! - Great job!
Today was...
a painful day, but I was happy at the same time.
The memories I made with them...
would be my own trophy from this mission.
JEONG MIN JUN versus Hash.
I was able to protect my choreography...
and take over Hash's choreography too.
She said I might be going home early.
I'm just getting started.
(I'll bring everything out in my brain.)
The director spot wasn't filled yet.
I really wanted to take the credit as the director.
My brain started doing its thing.
"How should I direct this performance?"
A new performance with features...
of MIN JUN's choreography.
I thought that approach might be cooler and more original.
I felt confident that I could put on...
a performance where all 40 dancers moving as one.
Hash wasn't able to take the credit as the choreographer.
So she'll have to work harder to get credited as the director.
All right. I'm going to teach you the choreography today.
First of all, this isn't my choreography.
I took down Hash in a landslide victory.
I totally beat her.
(MIN JUN is the best.)
I have to learn it too.
I was worried about how my dancers would think of me.
So I couldn't look at them.
Let's start from the top.
Inhale as much as you can.
I tried to make it look like I was doing my best to teach them...
while I deliberately held back.
(Flustered)
One, two...
This was a choreography workshop.
I wasn't required to teach them every detail.
One, two, three, four.
That's it. The steps. And boom.
(Unable to understand the moves)
MIN JUN's teaching was just awful.
When we're performing as a big group,
we have to execute the same moves in perfect sync.
Hitting the counts is super crucial.
(He's not counting the beats at all.)
So you put your right hand down...
right after we count six.
- Right after six. - I was frustrated.
So I intervened during the workshop and tried to clear things up.
Three, four, and a five. What was that?
- Three, four, and a five. - Three, four, and a five.
Yes.
How could you be a director...
if you can't stay on count?
Getting crafty was my strategy.
All right, here's what we'll do.
Hash, could you show us what you have so far?
- What? Me? - Yes.
MIN JUN kept trying to provoke me.
Of course, I feel threatened by her.
She's my rival. That's only natural.
Me? Why don't we do it together?
I'm not feeling well.
I'm not feeling well either.
But you have to lead your team.
It didn't feel good.
I didn't want to show him any moves I developed at all.
So I was going to dance exactly what he taught me.
My choreography is quite hard to learn.
(Cheering)
Wow
(Perfectly copying MIN JUN's choreography)
(A feast for the eyes)
I was surprised too. She was good.
After watching her dance, I was quite worried.
MIN JUN, when you were teaching the choreography, it was so clear...
that I was going to win.
Here's the biggest reason why Team Hash will win.
Everyone, check out that guy over there.
He's the youngest dancer of my crew, COME HERE, Yoo Seung Ho.
I got COME HERE to join us.
Based on the direction of your performance,
you may recruit up to ten extra dancers.
As for my strategy, I'm going to need my crew.
They've been executing my choreography...
and performing with me for years and on.
I don't think I can compare them to anyone else.
MIN JUN.
Be honest. Aren't you scared that you're going up against me?
But Hash doesn't have The Stories.
My strategy is recruiting my crew.
My crew takes pride in...
creating high-quality performances.
This is my choreography.
My crew will do a great job executing my choreography.
I'll bring them in and show people how great my crew is.
But there's one thing...
about MIN JUN that I consider as a real threat.
It's the impact Lip J will bring.
(Team JEONG MIN JUN's powerful weapon, Lip J)
Let's try it.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
(The dancers including Lip J are sitting on the floor.)
One, two, three, four.
(While they're practicing nonstop,)
(these dancers have been on standby for 30 minutes.)
The dancers are sitting on the floor because they have nothing to do.
Or they're just resting.
Okay.
Could you guys count with me?
- One, two, three, four, five, six. - One, two, three, four, five, six.
One, two, three, four...
I was wondering how he planned to utilize me in the performance.
Raise your hands if you're in the intro.
Could you come over here?
I want the rest of you to stand here...
(Do we have to count again?)
Wait, no. Let me finish this up quickly.
I'll call you guys in afterward.
When we were waiting, I would have appreciated it...
if he gave us a clear plan...
like telling us how long it would take.
He made poor and inefficient decisions.
Next...
Let me see.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
One, two, three.
(Stopping)
MIN JUN came up with a lot of ideas.
Let me show you the hand movements. One, two, three, four.
I changed them just now.
He tried something, and when he didn't like it,
he changed it.
But as for Director Hash,
she has a clear plan for her setups and choreography.
She runs the sessions more efficiently.
That's where I noticed the gap between them.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
I'm sorry. One, two, three...
To be honest, his teaching wasn't smooth.
When evaluating a director,
the overall composition and choreography matter a lot.
But how a director supports and manages dancers...
is another major part of their skill set.
Compares to Hash,
his ability as a director falls short.
(Kalvin, the leader of The Stories, is observing MIN JUN direct.)
Here's what I've noticed about you.
The biggest difference between you and the rest comes down to...
dancer management.
Gosh, it's really tough.
How do I manage them?
I'm not really used to managing new dancers.
I'm having a hard time figuring out what to do.
How is it for you?
It was my first time...
- directing 40 dancers. - Yes.
I don't know how to bring them together as one team.
I watched you today. And this question kept popping in.
"Will everyone enjoy performing your choreography?"
That question nagged at me.
(Feeling bitter)
There must be dancers who might not enjoy it.
(He kept fixing his choreography to no end.)
I don't know...
how to approach them or bond with them.
I'm so lost when it comes to that.
I really want to try it, but I don't know where to start.
What is it for you?
It's the sense of belonging.
It's nice to start with small things.
I'll give it a try.
Thank you.
(He finishes the phone call with Kalvin.)
(Sighing)
It felt like I missed a huge mistake.
I treated them strictly as colleagues.
I realized that...
I had missed a lot of things as a director.
(MIN JUN is deep in thought.)
I kept trying to figure out a way to bring my team together...
like a family
Hello.
Did you get my letters?
- Yes! - Yes!
I cried.
Thank you.
It was just a small gesture to express...
how grateful and sorry I was.
(He wrote letters from the bottom of his heart after their practice.)
I apologized for not giving them clear explanations.
I wrote a letter, so they'd open up to me.
Did you like the food?
- Yes. - Really?
How's the practice going?
- How's the practice going? - It's fun.
- Really? - Yes.
(Touched and proud)
We formed a bond too.
It felt like I became a director they could rely on.
I was so happy.
Team Hash will begin their rehearsal.
- Hello. - Hello.
It looks like they have experience in performing as a big group.
They have a dress code.
They're trained for competitions like this.
I remember her being super original.
I'm looking forward to it.
I read her synopsis and her strategy for dancer management.
She was definitely ambitious.
It's the clash between the ego and the unconscious.
The ego and the unconscious.
This is such a complicated idea.
It's indeed a profound idea to explore.
She can show all this just in 2 minutes and 15 seconds?
But I must say I'm curious about her approach.
Since she had formal dance training, her technique level must be high.
She might be able to show us a crazy performance.
MIN JUN, I gave it my all...
to beat you.
There's a technique I'd like everyone to try.
Five, six, seven, eight. One.
This is it.
Are you all right?
It's our secret move. We have to do it. How could we not?
It only takes a day to learn it, but it looks super advanced.
But other dancers rarely does this move.
I know a lot of these moves.
I'm certain that this move will work.
She used a professional-level move in this group routine.
The technique level is quite high.
We're not used to seeing moves like this. It's quite interesting.
The vision I had in mind was coming to life.
The details are just perfect.
There's a real thrill to it.
- Because they're in perfect sync. - Right.
It's clear that they practiced a lot for this.
It does make me think that watching this live will hit hard.
Good teamwork is crucial for us to win this match.
They're in sync.
It's as expected from The Stories.
They had perfect teamwork and great energy.
Their performance looked so complete.
We can't overlook The Stories' teamwork.
We have to keep pushing and making harmony...
more than The Stories. Okay?
The details, angles, and teamwork.
I can make sure we don't lose to MIN JUN.
Putting dancers on the railing is a novel idea.
They can pull it off because they're classically trained.
Seeing dancers on the second floor would grab people's attention
So the dancers on the second floor had to be in perfect sync.
But they're still making mistakes.
Dancers on the second floor.
Please try a little harder. You guys have to look sharper.
Let's try it. Go.
One, two, three, four.
You're a little late.
Let's try one more time. Let's start here.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Don't point your toes. Flex them.
Five, six, seven, eight.
No. Four, five,
- six, seven, eight. - This is all part of the process.
Your legs must come out on one.
Did you get that?
Putting your legs out before one... No.
One last time.
Let's try one more time.
We should do it again.
Let's try one last time. I swear.
Their mistakes are so subtle that others won't pick up on it.
But I can't tolerate that.
- I want them to be in perfect sync. - Bring them close.
- One, two, three, four. - I spent a lot of time on that.
"This is what real original choreography is."
"And this is how you put on a real performance."
I really wanted to show this to a certain someone. Who?
MIN JUN.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
(JEONG MIN JUN versus Hash)
- Team Hash, let's go! - Team Hash, let's go!
Okay. Let's go!
Let's have fun and leave no regrets. Okay?
- Yes! - Yes!
(Glancing over)
I know this for sure. We're going to win.
(Smirking)
It's a battle between two offensive players.
But I think Hash doesn't have...
the sharp offensive edge that we have.
He has never been my rival.
He never worked as a director.
He's just a choreographer.
Sure, Hash was my teacher once.
I can beat Hash.
Please come in now.
I won't leave any regrets.
I'm still confident that we'll win.
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go.
Let's go, Hash!
I'm nervous.
(Everyone's here.)
Now, we'll have the Last Run...
between JEONG MIN JUN and Hash.
Could both choreographers please come onto the stage?
- Hash! - Hash!
Everyone was screaming, "Hash is the best!"
That gave me so much strength.
- JEONG MIN JUN! - JEONG MIN JUN!
I really want to be the one who wins.
It's already a big match.
I'm really looking forward to this.
They're really preparing for a real competition.
I think MIN JUN's crew is going to win.
That crew's synchronization is no joke.
I have a feeling she did well. She's such an obsessive person.
What's the thing you're most concerned about?
MIN JUN's choreography was selected for this mission.
I feel like MIN JUN's choreography...
is a little lacking in energy...
I'm just speechless.
Energy and synchronization were the things I was concerned about.
That's why I said that.
I came to compete in this even though I'm a co-director.
(I came to compete in this even though I'm a co-director.)
I want to show...
that overwhelming moment of beating Hash as a director.
We'll see who's the best performer in Korea.
(A declaration of war)
He's tough.
It doesn't even make sense that we're competing against each other.
I hope you feel honored.
Hash is someone I'm destined to defeat.
I think Hash has the advantage over the co-director.
MIN JUN is a genius.
I thought MIN JUN was going to win.
- This is going to be hard. - It's impossible to predict.
I want to show a whole other level of performance.
I'm confident in my work.
I have faith in my performance.
Now, it's time for Hash's Last Run.
Are you ready?
- Yes! - Yes!
I'm looking forward to Hash's performance.
It doesn't get any more exciting than this.
Ready, fight.
Will we be able to see everything she has in her brain?
There'll be a lot there.
(UNBECOMING: Crash, Hash)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Iron": JEONG MIN JUN)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Dream State": JEONG MIN JUN)
("Iron" and "Dream State" performed by Team Hash)
- What's that? - Subconscious?
I got chills.
- Awesome. - Gosh.
Did they all hit that perfectly?
(Does that actually work?)
The technique...
Goodness.
How did she get them all to practice that?
- It's crazy. - No way.
(That actually works.)
(JEONG MIN JUN's signature choreography part in "Iron")
She's dominating it from the start with their synchronized moves.
(Their synchronization is crazy.)
(JEONG MIN JUN's signature choreography part in "Iron")
Goodness.
This really feels like a choreography competition.
They're good!
(They're mesmerized.)
What's that?
(This is it!)
She really came prepared.
That's so cool!
That's right, they should do that at least once.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
That's really powerful.
It's unbelievable.
She's a member of COME HERE.
She also has a great sense of texture in her movement.
That's right!
She directed this really well.
MIN JUN's signature part.
(JEONG MIN JUN's new signature choreography part in "Dream State")
That's good.
- They're really good. - Gosh.
(JEONG MIN JUN's new signature choreography part in "Dream State")
They're really sharp.
This gives me chills.
Nice.
What's going on?
The dancers from "Stage Fighter."
Are they dancers?
This is the best part.
That's right!
(This is what I'm talking about.)
(His eyes are shaking.)
Their techniques are just crazy.
The queen is here.
It feels more powerful because they have so many dancers.
They're good.
Those were three clean turns.
(They're shocked.)
What's happening up there? What's with the second floor?
- What? - What?
What's that?
What's going on?
That just gave me chills.
She's a genius.
That looks nice.
The piano keys look nice.
(Team Hash dancers: Yun Hyeok Jung, Park Jin Ho,)
(Jahyo, Jeong Min, Nancho, Hye Ju, Ione, Yeon Woo, Unu, Lorien, Kaze,)
(Milly, Lisu, Si Eun, Tuffy, Maddy, Seo Ho, Siko, Da Yoon, Ruslan,)
(Junki, Rudy, Seung Min, Hye Won, Sigan, Yu Bin, Paco, Sophia, Naya)
(A silence falls after the performance.)
(Exhaling)
They did well.
They did so well.
That was crazy.
I got chills.
What was that with the piano keys?
- That was really strong. - It's just crazy.
How did she even come up with such ideas?
I know, right?
The things in her brain are just amazing.
I think Hash is going to win.
Don't get discouraged.
We're the best.
I'm proud of it. We really put on a mega performance.
This was a real mega performance.
When it comes to the mega performance,
ours is much more dynamic.
She said she'll show us everything she has in her brain.
She really did.
I think it's going to be a tough battle.
Let's do this. Team MIN JUN,
- Team MIN JUN! - Team MIN JUN!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's go!
It's my first time seeing MIN JUN.
Is he 23 years old?
I looked MIN JUN up after hearing that he'll be on the show.
He was in The Stories.
I think that's why he can do this.
To come here at a young age.
I'm looking forward to what he'll do.
This is the starting point of a person who's growing.
Okay, those entering have to wait here.
You can enter here.
(JEONG MIN JUN runs off somewhere...)
(after checking the stage blocking.)
(He suddenly heads offstage.)
(Where are you going, MIN JUN?)
Let's start from the part David and Goliath face each other.
He went there because that's the judge's seat.
He's thinking about the judge's perspective.
Let's start with the face-off section.
(The rehearsal begins.)
- One, two, three, four. - There's a fight going on.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - The theme...
is David and Goliath.
David represents a small, seemingly weak boy,
while Goliath represents a giant.
I get inspiration from my own life...
for everything I create.
Everyone has had a time when they were the underdog,
and eventually, there's a moment when they overcome something...
they never thought they could beat.
It tells a story of David growing...
as he defeats the giant Goliath...
with nothing but his own conviction.
The underdog's rebellion.
I'll complete my story in a really cool way...
and beat her using my story.
I never imagined that David would be Lip J.
The key here is whether they convey the theme.
I wonder how they'll convey it.
When Lip J enters, the dancers open up a path.
She appeared.
(JEONG MIN JUN isn't satisfied with something.)
Producer?
(A brief pause)
I want there to be a single top light over here.
For this part,
we need a spotlight just on Lip J.
The scene only makes sense...
once the lighting comes in.
Lighting is really important.
You have to show where the protagonist is with lighting.
He made directions to make sure the lighting was set.
Let's start with the part where Lip J enters from the bamboo forest.
(Spotlight on)
- This looks way cooler. - It's different.
There's someone leading the story now.
We just need to watch.
It's saying, "Look right here."
If the lighting does 50 percent of the work,
the other 50 percent is our real weapon.
Our only weapon is dance.
Hash's strengths are her solid composition...
and those explosive moments that amaze you.
Since I know I can't beat her in those areas,
I'll set myself apart with the quality of my choreography.
We'll dominate with our energy.
So for my signature part,
I chose a small group of dancers with strong energy...
and designed it to really pull the audience in.
They're doing the same choreography,
but the formations are different. Their dynamics are so much better.
The depth and density of the composition are better.
Let's begin now.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Yes!
Their performance is really tight even in rehearsal.
I heard The Stories has an atmosphere...
where they relentlessly practice.
Can we do it with more power?
- Okay! - Okay!
One, two, three, four.
- That's the culture of that team. - Five, six, seven,
- eight. - They keep going full force.
One, two, three.
Seven, eight, one.
Let's do it one more time. One last time.
The dancers have to maintain the quality of the choreography...
for it to really shine.
The dancers practiced until the choreography was ingrained in them.
- We'll do it with the music. - Okay.
Will MIN JUN join?
- Will he be on stage? - Will he join?
(He joins the final rehearsal.)
Since he's good,
he just needs to do it once after doing the directing.
- Gosh. - I like the density there.
I can see the story now.
The quality is great.
It has a story.
(Exclaiming)
(The dancers gave it their all...)
(even through the final rehearsal.)
The rehearsal...
has ended for now.
(Exclaiming)
There haven't been many times in my life...
when a dance performance almost made me cry.
You created a masterpiece...
that's really among the best I've seen in my life.
Thank you so much.
We went full out 6 to 7 times from start to finish.
I could see them trying their best to put in more energy...
even when they had no strength left.
I could see that from where I was.
I was very grateful.
We did the best we could, with all our strength.
- Team MIN JUN! - Team MIN JUN!
(Bring up...)
(the energy.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go. - Okay, let's go!
Let's go!
Ambitious boy.
The choreography is his.
Now, we'll have...
JEONG MIN JUN's Last Run.
I trusted my team members,
and I was confident that we were going to win.
I'm not that concerned.
Ready, fight.
Is this a competition?
It's like a competition.
("David" produced by JEONG MIN JUN)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Iron": JEONG MIN JUN)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Dream State": JEONG MIN JUN)
("Iron" and "Dream State" performed by Team JEONG MIN JUN)
- Goodness. - Gosh.
That's what I'm talking about.
How are they so in sync?
This is a scam.
That's neat.
There's structure right from the start.
It feels like they're carrying a story forward.
Is he a genius?
It's so powerful!
Lip J!
Lip J is here.
It's so interesting how he cast her as David.
The formation is just beautiful.
The music is just too good.
The cinematic music makes it feel more like a movie.
Goodness.
It's MIN JUN's choreography.
(JEONG MIN JUN's signature choreography part in "Iron")
This is a feedback competition.
They're amazing.
They're really good with the formations.
That's so cool.
I think we were much better.
I like how dense it is.
That's right. Making the rhythm.
It's so cool.
Why are they so in sync?
(Getting nervous)
- It's a competition. - This is a real competition.
It's a competition.
- Lip J. - This is crazy.
Lip J is determined.
(The anticipation is building.)
That's cool.
This is just insane.
(Lip J's class)
What was the pop at the end?
It's the signature part.
That's right!
The Stories is just amazing!
I got chills!
(JEONG MIN JUN's signature choreography part in "Dream State")
Isn't that crazy?
What's with the energy?
MIN JUN...
That's right.
MIN JUN even acts now.
The energy and the output are amazing.
Their dancing is amazing.
How are they so perfectly in sync?
How is this possible in just a week?
(A world-class choreographer's rehearsal period)
How do you do that?
I got chills.
He's really smart. He does the parts that he can pull off.
He let the visuals do the rest. That's so smart.
- Goodness! - That's right!
It's so neat.
That part was nice.
MIN JUN is really good.
Let's go!
(Everyone is in shock.)
That's cheating!
Their energy and synchronization...
were concerning.
Let's go!
They're coming together through the group choreography.
This is a mega crew.
It's so neat.
This is like the VIBE Dance Competition.
(They move like one.)
(Exclaiming)
It's not over!
It's not over yet.
This part is nice.
They're insane.
The details.
(Looking concerned)
This is giving me chills.
This is crazy.
How did they get this in sync?
The texture is in sync.
(Breathing as one)
(He's startled.)
Crazy MIN JUN.
You're good, MIN JUN.
Seriously. He's so good.
Let's go!
(The JEONG MIN JUN vs. Hash match performances end.)
(Watch the comparison video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
That was great.
He's such an obsessive person.
I could say that was perfect.
It felt so short.
Why is it so short?
I guess it was because the choreography was good.
They're no joke.
This is moving.
If the public...
saw this kind of performance,
they'd go, "What is all this?"
That's why he wanted to come.
Right. These kinds of talents should come here.
Their highlight was clearer,
and they had a great overall structure of the performance.
- That's right. - Hash's team had a strong...
- sense of progression. - Right.
But the signature choreography...
MIN JUN was surely amazing at it.
His energy was clearly different.
So difficult.
- This one? - Yes.
- No. - Did you decide?
Yes, but no.
We watched them yesterday.
It seemed different...
watching them from this perspective.
That's why it feels difficult.
Very good, though.
Both choreographers, please come to the stage.
You're so pretty, Hash!
MIN JUN!
(Heated cheers for both of them)
We did good. Hash is the best.
The underdog's rebellion.
They'll have no choice but to acknowledge it.
How were they so different with the same choreography?
So difficult.
It was very good, though.
(A serious look)
(Whose name will be on the Director Credit?)
I really enjoyed both of your performances.
They were the kind of performances I really like,
so I was immersed in them.
First, speaking about MIN JUN,
I saw some truly exceptional impact in your performance.
The energy was so powerful, I was almost envious.
I also liked how you tried to condense that energy.
I was impressed by the moments where you explored...
the texture of the strings and the beats...
in such depth.
I also think the outfit was really well chosen.
The lighting added so much dimension,
making the choreography stand out, feel bigger,
and have even more impact.
So I thought it was a great idea and a great choice.
I was relieved. He noticed that.
"This isn't right."
I was worried.
MIN JUN was so...
I'm not sure if I can say this,
but you looked so beautiful.
(That's right.)
You're so beautiful, MIN JUN!
(Feeling shy)
My beloved muse,
Lip J, looked so different.
Thank you for transforming her...
into such an unexpected character that it allowed me...
to imagine her in a completely different way.
You brought out her hidden talent.
You showed great qualities...
as a director.
That's right, MIN JUN.
Who would've thought I could do something like that?
She's such a high-profile figure.
It felt like he used her just for that purpose.
I think this is also an element of directing.
When we saw Hash's performance,
we were a little worried about it.
"I'm in trouble. What should I do?"
That's what I thought.
This piece...
explores what humans have made of themselves in their pursuit...
of becoming something, and what they've lost along the way.
This is too difficult.
I think she tried to say a lot with it.
It's too difficult for the audience to follow.
I was worried about whether the message would come across.
The moment I saw the performance,
I realized I had nothing...
to worry about.
I think I'm good at creating standout moments.
I'm good at expressing things.
I really liked how you conveyed...
the emotion and essence of the dance...
that formed the foundation of your performance.
The last part where you end up on the stage with all those legs.
Visually, I thought that was the strongest thing.
You understand how to make simple movements.
You frame them the right way.
You take technical movement,
you frame stories around characters with it.
But it was the most visually fun thing that I saw,
and I'm just letting you know that.
Your performance...
felt more like pain and desperation for emancipation.
I was so immersed in it...
that I almost cried.
The way you portrayed the pain...
The quality was incredible. I was so immersed.
I could see that the choreographer had a clear goal.
It was a relief.
I was grateful that she noticed that.
It left me feeling a little unsettled.
To be clear,
this battle was surely for 1st and 2nd place.
That's clear.
The quality was really good.
I think this is going to be a real neck-and-neck battle.
I think the point of all this...
is to evaluate their abilities as directors.
The director's intention...
and the ability to convey that.
These two things meant a lot to me.
I think the person with more convincing movements...
was MIN JUN.
I think it's a moment where I can prove my abilities.
When Hash started,
I really thought that she was just going to win...
because I just felt like it was more powerful.
I'm so sure of it.
I'm going to win.
This match is so hard.
These people are no joke.
1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
Who will be the choreographer to showcase their work...
to the audience and see their name listed as a director...
on the Credit Board?
Let's see the result now.
(JEONG MIN JUN vs Hash, who will be the director?)
I think I'll win.
My goodness.
Hash is the best.
You're the best.
They're neck and neck.
His storytelling is really good.
I think MIN JUN will win.
She's simply on a completely different level.
Hash will win.
- JEONG MIN JUN! - JEONG MIN JUN!
- Hash! - Hash!
I felt like throwing up.
I deliberately didn't look up.
Because I thought I'd be disappointed.
(Shocking!)
(JEONG MIN JUN vs Hash, who will be the winner?)
(JEONG MIN JUN!)
(Hash!)
I felt like throwing up.
I deliberately didn't look up.
Because I thought I'd be disappointed.
(Shocking!)
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
(JEONG MIN JUN wins.)
It's JEONG MIN JUN!
(JEONG MIN JUN got his name on the Director Credit.)
(Screaming)
(An emotional hug)
(Clapping with a sense of regret)
Good job, Hash!
Well done!
I was surprised. It was shocking.
I couldn't believe it for a second.
- Team MIN JUN! - Team MIN JUN!
(An overwhelming surge of emotion upon facing the dancers)
(The team members are deeply moved as if they could feel him.)
A flood of thoughts and emotions washed over me.
David symbolizes...
a very small and seemingly weak boy...
who appears incapable of overcoming anything.
I faced a lot of criticism for being here...
as a co-director.
(He summoned the courage to enter the Directors' Lab.)
Wouldn't he be at the very bottom?
I think he's weak.
Gosh.
I think he'll be the first to leave.
He can leave.
Because he's still young.
Your parents are worrying about you.
He's still a baby.
Everyone had a similar reaction.
They weren't lying.
I haven't built as much experience as those people.
I'm a David among many Goliaths.
I was significantly lacking in that regard.
So it felt like a heavy burden, and I was very worried.
In a way,
I, a David who might appear inadequate and weak,
defeated the giant Goliath.
I naturally became emotional.
I was truly grateful to the team members.
- Don't cry! - Don't cry!
- I think I'm going to cry too. - Don't cry!
Well done.
(Well done, MIN JUN.)
Everyone cheered with one heart and one mind.
Is it okay for me to receive so much energy from these people?
(Though clumsy, he reached out to the dancers with all his heart.)
These are the people...
who helped me in a battle where I had nothing...
and it seemed impossible to win.
We became a family.
I mean it.
(Team JEONG MIN JUN finally became a united force.)
In fact, the quality of the work itself...
was very high for both of you.
But...
this is a broadcast.
I think Hash needs to be...
a little kinder.
Mass appeal was a significant factor for me.
Judging by the synopsis, the story was...
overly long-winded.
I wondered if she could capture this...
within such a short time.
The synopsis was too difficult for me too.
I thought Team MIN JUN was kinder in that sense.
The aspect of mass appeal was mentioned the most.
How much would people seeing this for the first time...
be able to understand without reading the synopsis?
Ultimately, it's about layers.
Can ordinary people get this?
Mass appeal?
My perspective on the performance...
differs slightly from that of the judges.
They frequently mentioned "mass appeal."
Actually, I had time to change it.
(At the time of mid-point review)
Is it really 4 to 4?
I won't change it.
The reason I didn't change it...
was that I wanted to win...
over the public.
Let's stick to what I have...
and show it as it is.
If it had been the competition I usually participate in,
I would have won.
No doubt.
- I'll... - Yes.
show them on the scene.
I'm serious. I'll show them.
Right away.
I think we put on an amazing performance.
Yes. So I'm really grateful.
I'll make you win...
a different competition in the future.
(We trust you.)
Thank you so much.
(Hash expresses heartfelt gratitude.)
(Next week)
(Why am I here?)
(It feels like being pushed out...)
(into a wasteland.)
(Are you ready?)
(Team BADA)
(It was a ritual intended to make the world dance.)
(Team INGYOO, screaming)
(Team BADA makes a sortie.)
(Team INGYOO makes a sortie.)
(I'm not afraid of the directors' fight.)
(Because there's a difference in physicality,)
(I have a better chance of winning.)
(There will be a battle of physique,)
(but that won't be a problem.)
(It's already over.)
(Dumbfounded)
(They're copying us!)
(Why does he keep acting so childish?)
(She's possessed.)
(It seemed like she was calling ghosts.)
(She looked like she was going to perform necromancy.)
(There's a dancer who lacks the fundamentals.)
(I'm like a stick.)
(Like a stick?)
(What am I going to do?)
(I've never prepared a performance...)
(with a dancer like this.)
(What's wrong?)
(She's wondering if you have any more choreography for her.)
(I don't want to know.)
(My goodness.)
(What? What's going on?)
(This isn't just a show. It's a competition.)
(If I mess up, I'll get cut here.)
(Please don't make a mistake.)
(It's a bit overwhelming.)
(Is my level too low?)
(BABYZOO vs NaiN)
(BADA vs INGYOO)
(A fierce Last Run toward the Director Credit)
(I'll take the Director Credit.)
(Honestly, I'm going to win.)
(My heart is going to burst.)
(I'll win no matter what.)
(Wait, NaiN. This time,)
(we're the mannequins.)
(Dancer?)
(It's the dancer!)
(We are becoming the dancers!)
(There is one director.)
(This is the Directors' Version of the Class Mission.)
(The second mission)
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(A choreographer will be eliminated.)
Gosh!
(The first choreographer to be eliminated)
(Final survival showdown)
(Application for on-site audience of "Last Stage: 24H")
(There is...)
(only one condition.)
(You have...)
(24 hours.)
(Are they crazy?)
(The final director holds the authority to decide...)
(which candidates are up for elimination.)
(Can they demonstrate the process of their efforts...)
(to the director?)
(Wouldn't that be the ultimate power?)
(I should become a director.)
(I don't want to be a dancer.)
(Directors are getting directed.)
("Over there, towards the back left. To the back.")
(If I have to put up with this,)
(I might as well just go home.)
(It's been so long since I've been...)
(directed by anyone.)
(Draft Creation Mission given to 10 choreographers)
(We need to find a good dancer for the Draft.)
(The 9 characters need to be clearly visible.)
(Vata should be the one to replace BADA.)
(Here is Vata who will play BADA.)
(I have to call them.)
(I called around right away.)
(I'll use Rozalin as BABYZOO.)
("Street Woman Fighter," Rozalin of WANT)
(As BABYZOO...)
(Who did Back Koo Young choose as BABYZOO?)
("Street Man Fighter," ROOT of 1MILLION)
(BADA, Simeez, Renan, BABYZOO)
(They all called me.)
(I need to get him before they do.)
(It's war.)
(Koo Young is the hardest.)
(Pick up the phone, Choi Young Jun.)
(Hello, Koo Young!)
(Hello, INGYOO!)
(Help me.)
(Can you please help me?)
(As a dancer?)
(I need you as Koo Young.)
(Mine has to be picked.)
(I'm really confident.)
(They'll like it.)
(I'm confident.)
(I must be the director no matter what.)
(The choreographic staging...)
(wasn't so good.)
(It was the standardized format...)
(required in K-pop videos.)
(I felt like he was looking down on me.)
(How can he look down on K-pop,)
(when he's so young?)
(Which part are you talking about?)
(I was expecting a cinematic presentation.)
(What about you?)
(Let's see how well you do.)
(The feeling like a cinema)
(It comes down to the variety of...)
(focal lengths and directorial choices.)
(It felt like a college midterm assignment.)
(He'll probably think it's really groundbreaking.)
(He'll probably think of himself...)
(as an idea bank.)
(2 candidates for the director position...)
(will be selected from among the 10 choreographers.)
(Videos of the two final draft versions released in advance)
(Who will be the 2 director candidates?)
(Why does it look like BABYZOO's choreography?)
(It strongly gives off a Back Koo Young vibe.)
(It’s got that total Director INGYOO vibe.)
(This was BADA's choreography. I knew it.)
(This gives off a Renan vibe.)
(Who will claim the final director spot?)
(The result of this...)
(is just amazing.)
(Worst Director Candidate)
(BABYZOO)
(I'm in trouble.)